MAYABAZAAR
[music]
[trumpets]
"As Gods and Goddesses
shower their blessings"
"Long live young Sasirekha"
"Long live, our dear girl"
"Blessed Revathi is thy mother"
"Blessing you to live happily"
"Balarama, who gives boons
before you ask is thy father"
"Blessing you promising
to fulfill all your wishes"
"Long live, our dear girl"
"Long live young Sasirekha"
"The blessed one, Rukmini Devi"
"is your aunt who dotes you"
"The almighty Lord Krishna"
"is your uncle who protects you"
"Long live, our dear girl"
"Long live young Sasirekha"
"The brave mother, Subhadra"
"is your paternal aunt who loves you"
"The Pandava prince, Abhimanyu"
"is your aunt's son who
considers you as his world"
"Long live, our dear girl"
"Long live young Sasirekha"
I'll hit the fruit just by
looking at its reflection.
Hit it.
[arrow whips and strikes]
[applaud]
Amazing!
Did you see?
Is it any honour to
hit it by watching it?
Well, I'll show you another skill.
Someone, keep this fruit on your head,
I'll hit it without hurting them.
-What?
-Oh no! We are scared!
How about you obstinate girl?
Let me see, hit it.
You might move out of fear,
close your eyes.
-Of course, I'm not scared.
-Whoa!
Is this what you're playing?
Aunt, move out of my way.
Never abstain from shooting the
arrow after aiming. It's my vow.
A vow?
Well, can you aim an arrow
as skillfully as I do?
Show it by shooting.
I'll shoot better than you.
Give it to me.
Aunt, can you shoot as
skillfully as my mother?
Why not? Come with me.
I'll show my skill before your mother.
Mother, hit the fruit.
It is actually you who is
responsible for everything. Come.
Subhadra
Subhadra...
Krishna,
When she is standing by
holding bow and arrow,
Isn't your sister-in-law looking
like Goddess Tripurasundari?
[chuckles]
What is it, sister-in-law?
Did you see what your son is up to?
Sasi is standing with a fruit on
her head and he's aiming to hit it.
What would happen if arrow hits her?
You fear is unwarranted,
my son will never miss his target.
Aunt, stand without getting scared,
I'll hit your nose pin...
-...without hurting your nose.
-What?
Well said, my nephew.
Krishna, I'm telling now,
The strength of all the five Pandavas
is equal to my nephew's strength.
Remember that.
Subhadra
Ask what boon will brother grant
for giving birth to such a brave son.
Make your wish, Subhadra.
Whatever it is, I'll grant it.
Let Sasi become my daughter-in-law,
what else can I seek from you, brother?
Is it any wish, Subhadra?
We decided she'd your
daughter-in-law the moment she was born.
-What do you say Rukmini?
-Yes.
-Subhadra, are you still doubting them?
-Still having doubt?
Here... Sasi is your daughter-in-law.
Is it okay?
[chuckles]
Go safely and come back safely.
Subhadra,
Give my special regards to Dharmaraja,
Bhima, Arjuna, Nakula, Sahadeva,
and their mother Kunti Devi, and Draupadi.
Go carefully, Subhadra.
You might forget us due to getting carried
away in that glory after reaching there.
You've said it with a smile.
Such words really hurt, sister-in-law.
Forget it.
Why don't you stay with us, nephew?
No, I'll not stay.
I'm taking Sasi with me.
Good, like father like son.
Yes... Yes.
Yeah, good! Come dear.
No. I'll go with him.
Let her come with us, sister-in-law.
You asked casually today,
But when that day comes,
you'll ask sternly
and we can't avoid sending her.
Well, let my daughter stay
with me till then at least.
-Come dear.
-No.
Satyaki, get her down.
-You can go later. Come down dear.
-No
We will come back again.
Come, get down.
Come dear.
Sasi, see you.
[birds chirping]
[music]
"She is a mischievous young girl"
"We'll tell her horoscope"
"She has the age of young beauty"
"This is the pride
because of her brother-in-law"
"She has the age of young beauty"
"This is the pride
because of her brother-in-law"
"Her brother-in-law is everything to her"
"She is a mischievous young girl"
"We'll tell her horoscope"
[music]
"Why are you angry to hear truth?
We'll tell truth as it is"
"We'll tell even if you object"
"Your suitor is man with
great skills and a genius"
"He's smart and witty too"
"She is a mischievous young girl"
"We'll tell her horoscope"
[music]
"He'll aim his arrow and hit the flowers"
"Our maiden gets enchanted"
"And invites him to her marriage"
"She is a mischievous young girl"
"We'll tell her horoscope"
[music]
Madam Sasirekha, Lord Krishna
has arrived from Indraprastha.
-Has my paternal uncle come?
-Yes, he wants you there.
You're right.
Brother, all the sages have
arrived at the Rajasuya yagna.
Dharmaraja missed you very badly as he
didn't find you in that honoured group.
See. It would've been
great if we had attended it.
Yes... Yes.
Brother,
Believing that you're the epitome
of truth and right choice for it,
Dharmaraja has sent this present to you.
What is it?
This is the magical tuffet
which makes people reveal...
...the absolute truth that is
hidden in their three time lines.
The popular belief is that
Sage Vishwamithra created this
to honour King
Harishchandra for his honesty.
Well, listen to the
influence of this object.
If we make anyone stand on this tuffet,
It will make them speak the truth about
their past, present and
the future thoughts
by bringing out their darkest secrets.
Oh!
I never even heard that this kind
of wonders existing in this world.
Satyaki, keep it safely in the Pooja room.
Come Sasi... Come.
Satyaki, where's the present
that is sent to Sasi?
Who sent it?
Will you give it without telling her?
Everything would be known.
Sasi, go to your room and
open this box privately.
It is a love vision, sister-in-law.
If you open the box,
it shows the thing you love the most.
Wow! Pandavas are really fortunate.
All the glory of Indra Loka
can be found in their kingdom.
Yes. Lord Indra's son
himself lives in that kingdom.
Rukmini, if my brother
Krishna wasn't with them,
neither Indra's son nor
Indra himself could do anything.
He made Dharamaraja to finish
the Rajasuya Yagna successfully.
He received the highest
honour in that great assembly,
and destroyed evil by beheading
Shishupala who spread hate.
Krishna, it is me who
should felicitate you.
Come here.
Brother
[music]
"Is it you?"
"Is it you who thought about me?"
"Is it you who called me?"
"Is it you who resides in
my heart and agitated it?"
"Is it you?"
"It is you who thought about me"
"It is you who called me"
"It is you who resides in
my heart and agitated it"
"It is you"
[music]
"It seems as if I'm awake in my dream"
"And my awake time
seems as if it is a dream"
"It seems as if I'm awake in my dream"
"And my awake time
seems as if it is a dream"
"I'm in a state of confusion as
I'm unable to understand"
"whether it is a dream or
the magic of Lord Vishnu"
"Is it you who thought about me?"
"Is it you who called me?"
"Is it you who resides in
my heart and agitated it?"
"Is it you?"
[music]
"By filling moonlight in my eyes"
"and making jasmines
bloom in my heart"
"By filling moonlight in my eyes"
"and making jasmines
bloom in my heart"
"You've melted my eyes and my heart"
"and left me allured and enchanted"
"It is you who thought about me"
"It is you who called me"
"It is you who resides in
my heart and agitated it"
"It is you"
It is the gift sent by
Abhimanyu. Did you like it, Sasi?
Why are you feeling very shy?
It was Abhimanyu you saw, right.
Did she see him?
Our daughter saw Abhimanyu.
It's really effective.
You too open and see it.
You're very excited.
You open it first.
Open it, sister. Come on
Wow! Diamonds...
Jewels, silks!
It seems like Goddess of Wealth is
everywhere. What is this?
What could it be?
Wealth is very dear to you. That's it.
I don't have any such desires,
don't know why it appeared.
It doesn't show anything simply, sister.
I think it is your desire because
you're standing close to me.
May be.
[chuckles]
But you won't accept the its outcome.
Try your turn.
I'll accept if it shows what you desire.
Okay, I'll do it for you.
What! Why did Duryodhana
appear? It is strange.
What's strange in it?
It is known to everyone that
Duryodhana is my favourite disciple.
Krishna, it's your turn.
Let's see who appears.
It is obvious that Arjuna would appear.
Do we've to see it, brother?
Rukmini won't mind.
So, look at it Krishna.
Okay. Whoever appears to
me, don't get freezed.
Because I really don't
know whom I like or hate.
[laughs]
What! Shakuni appeared
inviting for a game of dice.
Will great men appear
for nothing, brother.
Don't know what game he's planning?
Great humiliation! Brutal cheating!
Dharmaraja conducted the
Rajasuya Yagna to humiliate me.
He built Mayasabha palace to undermine me.
Vassal kings bowed
before him instead of me,
and presented him with gifts and tax.
And I myself distributed those gems
studded hampers to them and became a barl.
Above all, I was laughed
at by imperious Draupadi.
Before that humiliation burns me,
I'll sacrifice my life to fire.
Arrange the pyre.
O emperor! Why are you worried
when your friend Karna is here?
Blow the trumpets of war.
I'll kill Pandavas and repay my gratitude.
Well said Karna.
That's our immediate duty.
Duryodhana, why use an axe for
something that can be clipped with a nail?
Invite Dharmaraja for the game of dice.
I'll simply play the game,
effortlessly win their
kingdom and present it to you.
Winning and losing in game
of dice is decided by God, Uncle.
What if we lose?
May this inauspicious
words never come true.
My dice will never lose.
Test it. Come on.
Dushasana, tell me your number.
Two!
Wow uncle!
This is our immediate duty.
Karna, you tell now.
It's not heroic to hide our
strength and use contrivance.
No problem, Warrior Karna. Test my skill.
Two again.
Wow uncle!
Did you see Duryodhana?
An idea in the brain and dice in hands,
With them I can bring
a complete destruction.
You test me too.
-Third time is very important.
-Okay, I'll see. Same two.
No, wait. One!
Wow uncle!
Did you see? The dice fell one
hesitantly when you asked hesitantly.
-Invite Dharmaraja immediately.
-Yes brother.
That's our immediate duty.
Duryodhana, one more thing,
Dharmaraja is impulsive gambler,
he goes berserk on losing,
you make him stake not just
kingdom but his brothers,
himself and their wife
Draupadi too and lose them.
Now, it's your wish.
I hope you'll achieve
what you said, uncle.
Brother, uncle's idea is a cyclone.
A great cyclone!
[earthquake]
What's this bad omen, uncle?
Bad omen at Shakuni's place? No way!
This is a victory anthem for my plans.
Don't get scared.
Let all your fears vanish.
Even Lord Krishna,
who is biased in favour of the Pandavas
would understand the power of my dice.
Let's go.
[music]
"Did you hear this, Yashoda?"
"Did you hear about pranks of
your little mischief Krishna?"
"I don't know anything,
I wasn't here at all"
"What can we do about his behaviour?"
Is he the one who eats butter or mud?
"By supressing the sound of his anklets,
he enters house stealthily like a cat"
"He brings down the pots
that are tied to the ceiling"
"And drank all the milk"
"Ate all the curd"
"Swallowed all the butter"
"How can I single handedly eat them?
Does it happen anywhere?"
"Does it happen anywhere?"
"Did you hear it, mother Yashoda?"
"Did you hear the fabricated
stories of Gopikas?"
What? See how he is blaming us.
Can he be caught even if we want to?
"When all the ladies set a plan and
were waiting at every threshold"
"Anklet clinking was heard in one's home"
"Flute was being played in another's home"
"Aha! Then, what?"
"When we went inside to
check who the thief was"
"He jumped off from there magically"
"Ask your charming son how
he entered and escaped?"
"How would I know? I wasn't there"
"Where were you then?"
"Danced on the head of the snake, Kaliya
snake that poisoned the river Kalindi"
"I killed the snake and reared cattle"
-"I killed the snake and reared cattle"-Hey Krishna!
Hey Krishna... Mukunda...
Won't you hear my appeal for help?
"I don't have any other saviour than you"
"Who will help this woman in distress...
Hey Krishna,"
"Won't you see my pathetic condition?"
-"Please listen..."
-Krishna! What is this?
What's this?
What happened?
What would it be?
There is no bound for Kauravas atrocities.
Not only did they take away Pandavas
kingdom in their hexed game of dice,
but also they've humiliated them
and and were sending them to exile.
What! Such an injustice?
-So evil minded!
-It is the egoistic pride of the Kauravas.
We shouldn't tolerate this injustice!
Brother, give an order.
-I'll go with our army...
-Satyaki,
Don't rush off.
I too won't tolerate injustice.
Now, I'll go to Hastinapura and
teach a lesson to Kauravas,
and return the lost kingdom to Pandavas.
Duryodhana is my disciple,
he'll never go against me.
Get my chariot ready.
Come dear.
I've been fearing about
trickster, Shakuni's evil plans.
No matter whatever someone does, it is
we who have to face the consequences.
Don't worry Sasi.
I'm there for them.
Hail King!
We've received a message about your
Guru Balarama visiting our kingdom.
Sentry, take this for
bringing good news on time.
How is it good news, Uncle? I'm scared.
We don't know the reason of his visit.
Moreover, he's short tempered.
No problem, Duryodhana.
Best remedy for short temper is praise.
So arrange a grand
honour to Lord Balarama.
He will be pleased with your felicitation,
and grant you a boon without
even having a second thought.
Take it.
Get your son Lakshmana Kumar
married with his daughter Sasirekha.
With that, Balarama will be on our side.
Ultimately, Yadavas will be on our side.
And with that, Krishna will be left
with no choice but to join our ranks.
Wow Uncle!
That's our immediate duty.
Uncle, politically our plan is flawless,
but our Lakshmana Kumar
is more proud than his father.
Will he accept the Yadava princess?
Well, he will definitely accept.
That's my responsibility.
[humming]
-Sarathy
-My lord.
[whistles]
Wow! Amazing!
-My lord!
-Yes.
Great warrior, braveheart,
Lakshmana Kumar...
-Enough of your praise.
-Okay.
My lord, hear mine.
You're life is honourable than Abhimanyu's
Wow! This is real poetry.
Here, take it.
Then, hear this.
"Being exiled into a
forest is his ill-fate,"
"Having lavish life is your good fate."
Well said.
Hail prince!
-My lord, you've got visitor.
-Not now.
"In the battlefield, when a
Padmavyuha (Lotus strategy) is planned,"
"Abhimanyu knows only to go forward,"
"But you know how to turn back."
[laughs]
-My lord!
-Shh!
"Has he got your brain?"
"Has he got your ease?"
"Has he got your mastery of art?"
-"This is not a praise"
-Ha ha.
Sarathy... Sarathy.
My lord, they've praised
and accepted gifts.
These blabbering poets are
nothing compared to me.
-Hear mine.
-Yes.
"Two that side, two this side,"
"Abhimanyu's uncles"
"From either side,
they are just four."
"But for you,"
"You've got one less of hundred uncles."
What an army of uncles you have!
-"Wonderful..."
-Well said, Sarathy.
Dear Lakshmana Kumara!
Oh is it you?
You all may leave now.
Wow! You look very handsome.
A romantic hero indeed.
I'll tell you good news,
come sit here.
It is the attribute of a brave
person to listen standing.
Tell me.
Look, you're the prince
of this vast kingdom.
That's all?
Not just that,
you're the prince of princes.
Young king!
Young emperor!
Your father and I've decided
that we should get you married.
Then, I've decided too.
The proposal is also
from a very good family.
The bride is a world beauty.
Sasirekha, Balarama's daughter.
What a shame!
How can I become the son-in-law to
uncivilised liege king of Yadavas?
Impossible.
That's a danger.
We've heard that Abhimanyu loves her.
What!
Is it me who can't love her?
I'll marry any girl Abhimanyu loves.
I'll ensure that there are no girls
left in this world for him to marry.
Grandpa, I want Rekha.
-You're smart!
-Yes.
-Then I'll fix the marriage.
-Your wish.
Hail victory to you!
Epitome of truth!
Protector of the refuge seekers!
Generous man!
Saviour of the world!
Supreme lord of the world,
Sri Sri Balarama!
Hail victory to you!
[music]
Has he got your brain?
Has he got your ease?
Has he got your mastery of art?
-Who is it, Sarathy?
-You!
No... I mean Abhimanyu.
"Victory to you, O mighty warrior!"
"Victory to you, O romantic hero!"
"Lullaby." Stop your lullaby!
Okay.
My lord, come quickly and
seek blessings from Balarama.
Shame! Taking is seeker's trait.
-Giving is regal character.
-So be it!
My lord, if you delay like this,
you may not get Sasirekha.
You promised to bow to
your future father-in-law.
Not bow, I promised only to greet him.
-How to do it?
-It's simple, my lord.
-Fold hands like this...
-Shame! That's your habit.
So be it.
My lord, I'll show you.
You've seen Dharmaraja
greeting Bhishma, Dronacharya
and your grandfather, didn't you?
And you used to laugh jeeringly at him.
Even though it is little
difficult, bend like this
with profound humbleness,
-Bend like this... and that's all, my lord
-I can go down further, get up.
Come.
Moreover, the game of dice was played with
Bheeshma, Drona, Vidhura's permission
and in their presence.
If there was injustice
would they keep quiet?
Yes, winning fairly in the game of
dice is equal as just as winning a war.
I too accept it.
Not only you, even Dharmaraja
himself accepted it.
But Bhima got furious and
made vows of destruction.
Uncle, don't talk about that
blabber and hurt his feelings.
Let him tell, shamelessly made vows too.
-What did he say?
-To kill everyone.
He promised to split open my chest.
-He promised to drink my blood.
-What did l do?
Brother's order and my duty
to follow it.
-And Draupadi...
-Not just her relatives,
He was ranting that the world is on
his side and Kauravas fall is inevitable.
So I couldn't bear to hear it and said,
"Mighty warrior Balarama is on our side."
Then he said, "I'll break Duryodhana's
thigh as Balarama watches",
"what can that old man do,"
-"what can that Yadava do..."
-Aargh!
He's a rogue!
He's responsible for this enmity.
-It's not a sin to kill him.
-Calm down.
You're an elderly person,
who wishes for welfare of everyone,
I told you to relieve
my burden of my fear but
Guru, I don't want all
these fears and jealous,
I'll give you the entire kingdom
that I won in the game of dice.
Return the kingdom to them
and bring peace between us.
Unnecessary. It is sin to give
to those who don't deserve it.
Duryodhana, I'm granting you a
boon pleased with your conduct.
Make your wish.
Lakshmana Kumara,
you came at the right time.
Come son!
Touch Guru's feet and seek his blessings.
May you get married soon!
Duryodhana, your son is
ahead of you in humbleness.
He respects elders.
Never raises head also
before his father.
He has great devotion for you.
Those are the traits of a great people.
That will bring laurels to future kings.
Get up son!
What do you want?
He has been yearning for many years,
She's doing penance to make
your daughter Sasi his queen.
-You have to fulfil his wish.
-Happily granted.
Get up son.
Hail Lord Krishna!
Hail Subhadra Devi! Hail Abhimanyu!
Welcome Subhadra.
May you be blessed with marriage.
Are the Pandavas doing fine, brother?
Great men are fine
wherever they are.
Are you fine, dear?
Sasi! Did you see he
has become Sathyavan?
If he's Sathyavan, then she's Savithri.
Our girl is no less.
Rukmini, can't find
sister-in-law? Is she fine?
She belongs to olden times,
She's more sad than
Pandavas for losing kingdom.
Yes. If we are happy, she
will be happy too. Come in.
Come nephew.
I felt very pity on
seeing Subhadra, madam.
No grandeur of old times.
She came wearing jute sari
without any jewels.
As you sow so you reap.
-What can we do?
-Queen,
Subhadra Devi is coming.
Okay.
Champa, bandage my head.
[groaning]
Champa...
Come Subhadra!
Had a safe journey?
Please sit.
My bad time, I got headache when you came.
I couldn't even come to receive you.
I wanted to meet you immediately,
But brother Krishna and Rukmini
took me to their house, sister-in-law.
I don't mind which ever house you go to.
I don't have any such botherings.
Henceforth, all of us
have to stay here, right?
These twelve years...
Wherever we reside,
we don't lack any luxury.
You don't feel sad for it.
When is brother retuning?
How do I know?
Did he inform me before
leaving to inform his arrival?
Moreover, he's a short tempered man.
I'm scared that he may
pick up a fight there.
Oh no!
Sister-in-law, you're worrying
too much. Take some rest.
I'll come after brother arrives.
[music]
"In the auspicious time where our
glances met, why're you worried?"
"Why are you worried?"
"You're as beautiful as I had imagined"
"In the auspicious time where our
glances met, why're you worried?"
[music]
"In the auspicious time where our
glances met, why're you ecstatic?"
"Why are you ecstatic?"
"My dreams of meeting
me alone has come true"
"In the auspicious time where our
glances met, why're you ecstatic?"
[music]
"Songs and romance are
charming like songs of cuckoos"
"My love, you are work of art"
"Your gentle movements are dances"
"In the auspicious time where our
glances met, why're you worried?"
[music]
"Fluently making repartees like you sing"
"Showing your might on
your love in the garden"
"Your bravery has impressed the maiden"
"In the auspicious time where our
glances met, why're you ecstatic?"
"Why are you worried?"
Madam, your mother wants
to see you immediately.
Sasi, tomorrow is full moon day.
Don't forget about boating tour.
What's it mother?
Are you having headache?
Indeed your silly acts
are giving me headaches.
Why were you dancing around
with him in the garden?
What's wrong if I play with him?
Are you both little children?
You're young woman
and of marriageable age,
won't others laugh at us if you
roam with him before marriage?
Won't the elders of the
place find fault with it?
It'll bring bad name too.
What do you want me to do then?
I'm telling you to stop
going out with Abhimanyu.
Infact, don't even talk to him.
Follow my orders and be
my daughter. Understood?
[slams door]
[chukles]
[weeping]
Subhadra, what happened?
They say never go to parents'
home after getting ruined.
After seeing elder
sister-in-law's cold reception,
I'm rethinking of my arrival here.
What's this, Subhadra?
How can you think like this
despite knowing about her attitude?
She'll change after Balarama returns.
Come, your brother is waiting for you.
Wow! This one jewel will cost 10 lakhs.
If we have to value all these...
What's there in the value?
This is Emperor
Duryodhana's devotion on me.
He gave me a rousing
reception and felicitated me.
I granted him a boon
pleased with his devotion.
What did he wish for?
What did you grant?
Please tell me too.
How can I not tell you?
He asked to make Queen Revathi's daughter,
as the queen of future
king Lakshmana Kumara.
I said yes.
-But I'm worried about Subhadra.
-She might think anything.
Can we send our daughter
to forest for her sake?
As our daughter is really fortunate,
they made a request and you promised them.
And the burden on my heart has eased too.
But let us keep this confidential
till the marriage date is fixed.
-Why?
-You don't know anything,
Subhadra will create a
scene if she comes to know.
Oh! Alright.
Come dear... come.
Look, these gifts were
sent to you by Bhanumathi.
-I don't want it, father.
-Don't say like that, accept it.
Will you say no to gifts sent
by Queen Bhanumathi?
Who is she to send me gifts?
-Who am I to her to accept the gifts?
-Did you see her hot temper?
What's this dear?
They are also our well wishers.
How can they be, father?
Anyway I'll not accept it.
-Sasi...
-You keep quiet, I'll cure that itch.
What's your arrogance?
Will you walk out on your father?
When Kaurava King sends gifts
to honour you, will you belittle them?
I didn't belittle them.
Those evil people sent gifts
to insult you, me and all of us.
What? Who taught all these bad ideas?
Rukmini and Subhadra?
I don't like all this.
Don't ever go to their home
again, don't even talk to them.
You're my daughter.
You must obey me. Be careful.
[sobbing]
[slams door]
Sasi,
What are you waiting for? Come quickly.
Shh!
[women laughs]
The door is locked,
how should I come out?
Shh! Jump, I'll catch you.
How am I to come up again?
Sasi, I'll make a ladder
with arrows. Climb down.
[arrow swooshes]
[music]
"In the intoxication"
"The world is rocking"
"The world is rocking and fumbling"
"In the intoxication"
"The world is rocking"
"The world is rocking and fumbling"
"In the company of
graceful stars and moon"
"With pervading soft moonlight"
"With great speed"
"In the company of
graceful stars and moon"
"With pervading soft moonlight"
"In the caressing gentle breeze"
"filled with fragrance of lovely flowers"
"In the intoxication"
"The world is rocking"
"The world is rocking and fumbling"
[music]
"Sweet memories are
incited by dreams"
"Passions are charged up"
"In this shine"
"Sweet memories are
incited by dreams"
"Passions are charged up"
"In this mesmerizing ride"
"on boat of love"
"In the intoxication"
"The world is rocking"
"The world is rocking and fumbling"
[playing veena]
-Come with me.
-Where to?
I'll tell you.
Come.
Greetings, my lord.
Princess Sasirekha and Abhimanyu
are riding in a boat, my lord.
How did she go out?
Come.
[music]
"Making this romantic
world to pitch for love play"
"This pleasant
sweetness of love is prompting"
"This pleasant sweetness..."
"Making this romantic
world to pitch for love play"
"This pleasant
sweetness of love is prompting"
"Bringing peace to
everyone's agitated heart"
"With the lovely pranks of
the mischievous lord"
"In the intoxication"
"The world is rocking"
"The world is rocking and fumbling"
Poor soldiers!
They mistook them for our children.
Wonder of modern times!
What's these late night boat
rides for Rukmini at this age?
It is not the time but
the effect of nature.
In this moonlight with cool
gentle breeze blowing... Wow!
Anyway we have come so far,
let's go for a boat ride.
Come.
"In the intoxication"
"The world is rocking"
"The world is rocking and fumbling"
Wonder of modern times!
What's these late night boat
rides for Revathi at this age?
Love has no logic!
Hail the mighty majestic,
his royal highness!
Hail the mighty majestic
his royal highness Lord Balarama!
Hail the mighty majestic,
his royal highness!
Stop!
I'll get you gifts.
Praising me coming to my place.
Then what? You're the supreme lord!
Yes... but I didn't expect you so early.
Why should you think, brother?
You're kind hearted boon giver,
don't know what boon you granted them.
May be he's here to remind
you, lest you may forget it.
Why should I remind him, Krishna?
The moment he granted
the boon we were blessed.
Yes... Great men don't come for nothing.
Brother...
Whatever it is, I'll not tolerate
if he plays game of dice with you.
Why are you so scared, Krishna?
It is obvious that your
brother will win the game of dice.
He's epitome of honesty.
But if it is proved you're dishonest,
you'll have trouble from him.
It's good for you to be careful.
Though I'm younger it
just my sweet warning.
Did you see how Krishna is
threatening with his wit?
No, whenever he meets intelligent
men like you, he gets little shaken up.
Welcome.
This auspicious time is fixed according
Lakshmana Kumar's horoscope.
The event of wedding of Sasirekha
will be an event that world will
remember for a very long time.
The power of the
auspicious time is very strong.
You've decided the auspicious time too.
Of course. As soon as you said okay,
Bheeshma, Drona and Vidhura
wanted this to happen at the earliest
So they've sent us by fixing
this date and time of marriage.
If elders had fixed this, I'm
sure it'll be very important.
Why are you thinking, brother? Go ahead.
So be it.
I think our priests are checking
for the best auspicious dates.
Wow! Great astrologers!
They are very renowned astrologers.
There's nothing to think
about this auspicious time.
And even there is nothing
doubtful about this auspicious time.
But still,
We're checking planetary movements
according to the bride's horoscope.
Shukracharya,
the guru of demons is casting a bad eye.
This may create problems and difficulties
in the lives of the newly weds.
Yes, astrology always says
right and bitter truths only.
We must take only
the gist of it lightly.
You've to take problem
here as love problem.
Difficulties here mean many children.
But this is bad time.
Astrology says marriage
in these times is impossible.
You need to be presented
for your scholarliness.
But your astrology works
for ordinary people only,
not for Kauravas who are
brilliant and fortunate men.
May be but when Saturn is in this room...
[chuckles]
Our Shakuni who is equal
to a lakh Saturns is here,
so why bother in which room the Saturn is?
Accept it. It's their tradition.
Brother, their haste is ours too.
I too agree for this proposal
and the time fixed by them.
Only if you think we don't
have much time.
Krishna, when you're taking all
the responsibility in your hands,
The time will never run short.
I don't have that fear.
Alright. We shall fix
the wedding at this time.
Amazing!
Sasirekha madam is very fortunate.
She's going to wed Prince,
Lakshmana Kumara
and become the daughter-in-law
of Queen Bhanumati...
-Champa
-Madam.
Be careful.
Mind your words. Get lost.
[metal vessel tumbles]
What's this barlishness, Sasi?
How humiliated I would be if
people come to know your attitude?
I plead you. Get groomed and come now.
Grandpa Shakuni will bless you.
I don't want any blessings.
I'm not interested in this wedding at all.
Don't you say that. It is the
proposal which matches our status.
And it is the wealth which came for us.
Your dad gave his word to the
emperor for the welfare of you.
Even your Uncle,
Krishna accepted this proposal.
It is a lie. Everything is a lie.
Your uncle himself sat with
them and approved the proposal.
Let me ask him to say that to you.
-I don't want anyone to tell me anything.
-My Queen
Subhadra and Rukhmini have arrived.
Everyone was holding grudge on me.
What sin did I commit?
Is it justice to break a promise of making
Sasi my daughter-in-law, brother?
Is it breaking a promise?
He told it just like that to his sister.
Will it be same as granting a boon
to emperor Duryodhana in his court?
Not only that, you're making a
wedding alliance with of our enemies.
Did you think it's a great insult to me?
How my husband his
brothers look down upon me?
If you think there would be such
treatment, then don't go there at all.
There's nothing short
in your respect here.
Enough of your respect for me, brother.
I'm telling you the last time,
If Sasi doesn't become my daughter-in-law,
I'll not stay here even for a moment.
Is this how you're going to threaten us?
Do you want my daughter also
to be in parents' home like you?
Sister, leave about Subhadra.
Think about our daughter.
It is we who filled her
thoughts since childhood.
Sasi hopes that Abhimanyu
will become her husband.
If you marry her to someone else,
what will become of her life?
Do you know about a daughter more than me?
You would know had you
given birth to a daughter.
Would you say these morals then?
Revathi, keep quiet.
Whatever it is, this wedding
would be conducted as scheduled.
I don't want anyone
to stop or threaten me.
Surely you do, brother.
You're ruining two young
people's lives cosnciously.
I didn't think you'll be so obstinate.
Making your sibling sad
wouldn't just go waste.
May be you think wealth of Kauravas
is greater than courage of Pandavas.
It will never be true.
Are you threatening me with
their bravery, Subhadra?
Their bravery doesn't need me,
my disciple Duryodhana is enough.
Even 1000 Bhimas and 1000 Arjunas
are nothing compared to him.
Uncle, mind your tongue.
Though my father is not present, I'm here.
-What will you do?
-What will I do?
Abhimanyu, will you bring an insult
to me by going against your uncle?
This is not a mutiny.
I'm standing bravely on my ground.
Uncle, if Kauravas are
as brave as you say,
tell them to come along
with Lakshmana Kumara,
I'll drive out Duryodhana,
Dushyasana, Karna and Shakuni,
and their armies to Hastinapuram,
I'll take Sasi as my wife
in open competition.
If you and your friends have the courage,
announce a Swayamvara.
You'll know who Sasi belongs to.
Abhimanyu,
why are you throwing challenges?
If you are really a brave man,
would you stand here and throw challenges?
Subhadra, you're a brave
wife and a brave mother.
I didn't expect you to be so weak.
You understood Balarama's intentions,
right? Why do you still make a scene?
There is no one here to
to listen to your appeals.
You can go wherever you feel like.
Sure, brother.
The day when you honour
bravery but not wealth,
I'll step here again only on that day.
Aunt!
-Aunt!
-Where are you going, Sasi?
-I'll also go with aunt.
-When I'm still alive?
Don't get smart with me.
Come.
-Aunt.
-Sasi, what's this?
Dharuka,
Subhadra and Abhimanyu
are leaving to Dwaithavanam.
But you've to take them to Ghatotkacha's
ashram without informing them.
That's all.
[music]
"O God"
"Your illusion is amazing"
"Your illusion is really amazing"
"It's a himiliation to one
and happiness to another"
"And it is entertainment to
you who knows everything"
"Who is your person and who is above you?"
"Even the fate doesn't know it lord!"
"Your illusion is amazing"
[music]
"The world in a tug of war
between happiness and sorrow"
"is your playground"
"Your tales of playing and illusions"
"The people who know
about them are fortunate"
"Your illusion is amazing"
"O God"
"Your illusion is really amazing"
[music]
[trumpets]
Hmmm...
-Dundubhi!
-Present sir!
-Dundhura!
-Ugra! Bagra!-Present sir!
Present sir!
-Gaggolaka!
-Present sir!
-Gandaragolaka!
-Utchhasura!
-Present sir!
-Jatasura!
Rambu! Jambu!
-Rambu! Jambu!
-Present sir!
Present sir!
[yawns]
If you study well as I instruct,
I'll clear your language difficulties.
If not, Ghatotkacha will
come and thrash you.
Master, our life is
linked with your lessons.
Come on, teach us.
Repeat!
Su... ou... chus
Group repeats:
Am... ou... chus.
Dra... bhyou... bhis.
Group repeats:
[groans]
Je... bhyom... bhyas.
Group repeats:
Je... bhaya... bhass.
Oh Shiva!
Group repeats:
Shh!
-Hey Rambu! Bhyam.
-Bhayam.
-Jambu.
-What?
-Bhyas
-Bhass.
Oh Shiva!
Group repeates:
[groans]
[groans back]
You are called leaders.
Can't you even repeat?
Can't you pronounce?
What if we can't pronounce? We will dance!
"Here we go around, now we jump!"
-Now we jump! Now we jump!
-Hey Rambu Jambu!
[indistinctive loud singing]
-Hey Jambu!
[drums playing]
Ghatotkacha
-Ghatotkacha
-Hail leader!
"My flag must flutter"
"on all eight directions"
"Every demon, devil,"
"elf on earth must worship me"
"Wherever the place be"
"wonders must happen upon my orders"
"Even Gods and angels must say,"
"Hail Ghatotkacha!"
"I must rule this world"
"I must acquire all the wealth"
"I must make all our
relatives achieve greatness"
"...and get all the glory!"
Hail Leader!
Chinamaya, my associates don't
need this education any more.
They must learn the history and get
knowledge of friends and enemies.
They should protect
friends and eat enemies.
Hail Leader!
-We'll eat!
-We'll eat enemies.
Son!
-Son! Son!
-Mother!
I told you not to do this.
Whom are you attacking now?
There is no war presently.
But I'm preparing for it, mother.
King Bhimasena is your husband, my father,
This is my preparation to wipe out those
evil Kauravas who betrayed them, mother.
-That's a good deed, my son.
-Hail mother!
-Hey Rambu
-Yes sir!
-Hey Jambu
-Our army must grow with every passing day
-Hail Leader!
My dear associates,
develop an army of your own.
Imprison anyone who crosses our path.
-Hail Leader! [chariot moving sound]
-Aargh!
Who is this charioteer
who dared to enter my area?
-Kutasura
-Hail leader!
Who is he?
Make him say his name
and ask him to seek refuge.
Hail Leader!
I consider only those who seek
my refuge as my associate. Go!
[demonic spell]
Go back and seek refuge.
Dharuka, what are these screams?
We can't see anyone.
[screams]
Why can't see anyone?
Looks like magic world of demons!
Dharuka, we haven't taken
the wrong route, right?
This is right way.
We've entered it knowingly.
Or shall we go back?
Turning back is not our way. Go ahead.
Go back or seek refuge.
Why are you screaming invisibly?
If you've guts, appear before me,
I'll destroy your magic.
[screams]
-What's this? His magic is scary!
-Don't fear, keep going.
Hey lllusionist!
My arrow will kill you!
[groaning]
I surrender!
Victory is yours!
Carry on.
-Jambu
-Yes sir.
The Pandavas are friends.
It means our people.
Repeat now.
The Pandavas are frendz
Not frendz, say friends!
Say frendz! Not frendz.
King, he's teaching me now!
Ask him to say friends.
Why? We'll know our people
with that word, king.
Enough!
Knowledge is more
important than scholarliness.
Present him rope award!
Come on, put!
-Hey Rambu
-Yes, sir.
The Pandavas are friends.
What do you call their enemies Kauravas?
Anti frendz... Anti frendz.
You and your brain!
My lord, he has produced a new
word foe as antonym of friend.
Yes, how words develop
without anyone producing it.
-Award him with two!
-Two? Okay put!
Chinamaya,
teach them what you call Duryodhana,
Dushyasana, Karna and Shakuni together.
Well, Bad quartet! Repeat it!
Yes. Ba...
Come on, say it! Bad quartet!
Bada quarateet!
-Badaa quaraateete!
-Oh my God! Oh my God!
Oh my God! Oh my God!
-Shh!
-It's wrong to split a word.
-Why is it wrong?
We must split and kill those
quartet like they pronounce.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
[laughs]
My lord...
[groans]
Some human busted me.
He's young and tempered.
Human? A young man?
Strange! Strange!
-Hey Rambu
-Yes, my lord.
-Hey Jambu
I can't tolerate this any more.
Finish him with your magical powers.
-We'll knock him down and...
-And bring him to you.
-bring his dead body, my lord.
-Go now.
Wait!
I feel like seeing the young warrior.
Bring him alive.
What do you say, Chinamaya?
Go!
[demonic spell]
I'll spread from that side,
you spread from that side.
[demonic spell]
What's this danger, Dharuka?
Forest fire!
It's coming fast towards us!
Go back or seek refuge.
Looks like it's illusion!
-What do we do now?
-This is a wind missile!
[groaning]
[guffaws]
Hail young hero! I appreciate you!
Your courage has moved me.
You are very enchanting.
Atlast you've gathered
courage and stood before me.
I'm also very happy. Come.
Hey boy! Your innocent face is
cooling my anger.
Your are a match to fight me.
Tell your name and seek refuge,
you'll become my associate.
Are you a warrior who
pleads on seeking refuge?
I'll make you seek refuge.
Watch out!
Aargh! You really hurt me!
But I don't feel like hitting back, boy!
Tell that you are incapable.
You can't just call me as a boy
and claim yourself to be an elder.
Show me your power.
I'm not getting enraged no matter how much
you provoke me. I feel pity about you boy.
O mother, ask your son to tell
his name and save his life.
-Son! Tell him your name.
-Impossible!
Scared of enemy and tell my name? No way!
Hey demon king!
Unable to win over me,
you've made this evil proposal.
You're cunning, coward,
-you don't have any pride.
-Hey! What's your arrogance?
You're going against me as if you're
here to test my power. Watch out!
[guffaws]
-Oh! He made our leader lose his mace.
-Oh! Suprising!
[guffaws]
[bangs]
Aargh!
[thud]
Abhimanyu... Abhimanyu!
My son.
He's just unconscious, madam.
Ensure the demon not attacks
again before he regains conscious.
"I'm Lord Krishna's sister
who rules over heaven and hell"
"I'm Arjuna's wife who is the
mightiest warrior with magical arrows"
"May this arrow kill the enemy"
and protect the heir of Pandavas
Forgive me mother, I seek your refuge.
It's an unwittingly committed mistake.
Please forgive me, mother.
I'm Bhimasena's son, Ghatotkacha.
-Is it?
-Yes, mother.
It's an unwittingly committed mistake.
Please forgive me.
-Hey demon! Wherever you may be...
-Well...
Victory be yours brother!
I'm here under the
protection of mother.
Abhimanyu, he's your
elder brother Ghatotkacha.
-Huh?
-Yeah!
-Hi elder brother!
-Hi younger brother!
It is surprising!
I'm very elated, mother.
Extremely elated.
You've made a rare visit
to us. Got you at last.
I'll not leave you.
Son, I told you not to wage
any war. What's this commotion?
Who are these humans?
Why are you arresting them?
Not arresting but hosting, mother.
Do you know who she is?
She's queen of uncle Arjuna!
Subhadra Devi!
-Sister Hidambi.
-May God bless you, sister.
I'm seeing you for the
first time. Is he your son?
Yes, mother.
God bless you, son.
God bless you.
-Hey Rambu
-Yes, my lord.
-Hey Jambu
They are our friends!
frendz.
Bow to them!
Frendz.
-Madam Subhadra, I'll take leave now.
-See you.
-Hey Rambu
-Yes, my lord.
-Hey Jambu
Our friends must be
given a grand reception.
Arrange songs, dance and music!
Come... come.
Mother...
Brother...
Elders... Elders!
Why should we these
elders with us for the wedding?
Drona, Ashwathama and
Kripacharya are not even our relatives.
I struck off their names
at the begininng itself, brother.
Bheeshma and Vidhura are our grandfathers
amd we belong to their lineage.
Lord Krishna will definitely
ask why they haven't come.
What will be your reply, uncle?
What should we answer?
They are still on Pandavas side.
Hence, let's them that old men
are paralyzed or can't move.
Well said, Karna.
I struck off the oldies too.
By striking off all the names and if it is
just four of us who attends the wedding,
How could it be any glory?
Not just four of us, Duryodhana. All
your brothers would attend the marriage
All the hundred brothers are
enough, it will be very grand,
and we would can keep our word too.
Well said Uncle!
Then, what is our immediate duty?
Travel preparations.
Hail lord!
The grandfather must come
immediately to Lakshmana's room.
Uncle, go immediately.
He may've created a new problem.
No need, he himself is here.
Come son.
Character of youth!
You'll have a feeling of
socializing as your wedding is fixed.
Yes grandpa, I don't have any stage fear.
I'm came here because
I can speak in public.
I don't want to get married.
-What?
-Yes, father.
It's not bravery
without seeing the bride.
I was expecting this, Duryodhana.
Our boy forgot about this
respecting our decision.
Yes, now I remembered it.
Yes, grandson.
Princes like you must go and see any girl,
if you find them beautiful,
you should even fight Gods and win them.
Indeed.
Abhimanyu may hesitate but you wouldn't.
Let's go to Dwaraka immediately,
Upon reaching the bride's house,
I'll call the bride and you can meet her.
I'm sure you will like her.
Even if I don't like,
I must meet the bride before our wedding.
That's my vow!
-Alright, grandson. Get ready to travel.
-I'm always ready to travel.
[applaud]
-Son
-Mother
What's this senseless dancing?
Arrange a play that preaches moral.
I'll appreciate you.
You heard my mother's order,
right Chinamaya?
Yes. We have the story
of Mohini- Bhasmasura,
which preaches the moral about consquences
of granting boon to evil persons.
I'll arrange it. See and enjoy.
[casting a spell]
[music]
[applaud]
[knocks]
Sasi...
It's me! Open the door.
They came to get you dressed as a bride,
Why did you send them
out and closed the door?
Why don't you talk to me?
Open the door.
How many times do I've to tell you?
I don't like this marriage.
Sasi, there is nothing to do
with your consent or mine.
Don't think your protests
will cancel this marriage.
The groom's family is coming.
Your objections will not
be accepted. Be careful.
Get through it happily.
Happily?
You dashed my hopes, broke my heart,
and spoilt my mind.
Infact I don't want to live at all.
What are you saying, Sasi?
What happened, sister?
What could it be? Your ideas which you've
pitched into her mind since childhood,
are taking toll on me now.
Don't get angry, sister-in-law.
She is just a little girl.
Give her little time to calm down.
You will see her excited and
enthusiastic by tomorrow.
Whatever, Krishna. I'm always optimistic
because you solve all the things.
It's your responsibility to conduct
this marriage without any hitch.
What is this, Sasi?
[weeping]
Alright, you will know it tomorrow.
[music]
"I'm living just for you"
"In this sorrow of separation
and hopelessness"
"I'm living just for you"
"Even if moonlight turns dark"
"and if there is complete
darkness in my heart"
"I'm living just for you"
[music]
"Isn't separation of sorrow a solace?"
"Isn't thinking of love always sweet?
"In this time of separation,"
"Can't you see our love getting stronger?"
"I'm thinking about you"
"In my heart and mind"
[music]
"Though my heart leaves with you"
"And my hopes vanish"
"I keep thinking about our love"
"and holding on to this life"
"I'm living just for you"
[music]
"In reality or in a dream,"
"I worship you as my lady love"
"Even if the entire
world turns against me"
"You're mine"
"I'm thinking about you"
"In this sorrow of separation
and hopelessness"
"I'm living just for you"
What?
He gave his word to get
Sasi married to Abhimanyu,
And he's he shamlessly breaking it to
get her married to Duryodhana's son?
How could Balarama being
your own brother insult you?
What can we do now, sister?
We lost all our wealth, right?
You just lost wealth not courage.
How can he even think like that?
How can the wealth worshippers
see courage, sister?
He even insulted by saying 'The Pandavas
are nothing compared to Kauravas'
Hey Rambu.
Hey Jambu.
Blow the war bugle!
Looks like son has heard us.
Son... Son.
My dear associates,
get ready with your armies and weapons.
We are going to war now.
Hail leader!
Whom are you waging a war against,
brother? I'll also join you.
Why do you toil when I'm there, brother?
My dear associates...
Son... Son!
I heard you, mother.
Not only did he break the promise,
but joined hands with those evil Kauravas
and belittled my world famous father.
These Yadavas are very proud and arrogant!
I'll avenge them by
wiping off both the Yadavas and
the Kauravas together in one go.
"They've grew contempt"
"and commited a terrible betrayal."
"Till I see their end"
"I, mighty Ghatothkach won't sleep"
"I pledge to wipe off
the entire Kuru clan"
-"and end their treachery"
-Hail leader!
Hail leader!
Son, it is the same if either of you
wages the war against my brother.
Won't it bring a bad name to me?
Then, I'll go to Hastinapuram
and finish at least Kauravas.
You can't kill them, son.
Your father has made vows.
The Kauravas must live to die
in the hands of the Pandavas.
Did you see, brother?
Our mothers' words have
made our strengths useless.
Follow my orders, son.
I'll appreciate you.
Go to Dwaraka,
use your magical powers
and bring Sasirekha here.
I'll get her married to him.
Good, your order will be
implemented, mother.
I'll go immediately.
-My dear associates!
-Hail leader!
-Son!
-Mother!
I'll let you go only if you promise,
not to hurt or harm anyone there.
-My brother, Sri Krishna...
-Is he a friend?
My respects to him.
-Upon reaching there, meet him...
-Not just meeting, worship him.
He'll be pleased.
-He will tell you the plan.
-So be it.
Hail mother!
Hey Brother! You shall protect
them till I come back return.
As you say, brother.
Hail leader!
[humming]
What's this?
Move I say. Move! Who are you?
[groaning]
[people laughing]
How am I to find Sasirekha among
them? How can I identify her?
I came without knowing any details.
I'm in the same dilemma my
uncle Hanuman had in Lanka.
"May you live forever and be happy"
"What's on the other side is not here"
"What's here is not
there on the other side"
"What's on the other side is not here"
"What's here is not
there on the other side"
"I'm there on the other side"
"It's me even in here"
"I'm there on the other side,
it's me even in here"
"May you live forever and be happy"
"Big fish will eat small fish"
"Big illusion will envelop smaller one"
"That'll vanish.
This will vanish."
"May God bless you"
"You came without information
and you'll go unnoticed"
"This is enlightment"
-"This is enlightment..."
-Hey grandpa.
Your enlightment is good, but
tell me who you really are?
-Oh! Is it you?
-Yes.
Don't you know who I am?
That's why I'm asking, right?
An ignorant person will
not learn even if taught.
Hey grandpa! Stop your argument.
I don't care who you may be,
Just tell me,
where can I find Sasirekha?
What! Asking my help and shouting at me.
Tell me your name and seek
refuge humbly. I'll show you.
Hey grandpa! Who do you think I'm?
Be careful.
I can't hold my anger long,
I'll drown you and your
Dwaraka in the ocean.
Wow! Are you very powerful?
Why don't you tell me that?
You needn't do such great things,
I'm old and can't walk.
Carry me, I'll show you Sasirekha.
That's better. Get up!
"May God bless you!"
You're so heavy!
You threatened to drown Dwaraka.
Can't you carry me?
[chuckles]
Carry me son... carry me.
Did you eat elephants for dinner?
What's the magic?
"Big illusion will envelop smaller one"
"That'll vanish.
This will vanish."
"I'm there on the other side.
It's me even in here"
"I'm everything"
Oh! I got it! I bow before you!
I bow before you, Lord Krishna!
Bless you!
I'm blessed, waiting for your order.
Your next duty is...
Tranfigure yourself as Sasirekha
and get married to Lakshmana Kumara.
Teach the Kauravas a lesson.
Divine instruction!
Myna,
From now, you're his favourite maid.
No problem.
-Can I take leave now?
-Be careful, nephew.
Myna, show me the way to my harem.
Madam Sairekha...
Madam Sasirekha...
Hail Lord Krishna!
Hail mother!
Wow! What a beauty!
Your daughter-in-law is very beautiful.
-You didn't make a mess there, right son?
-No mother... not at all.
Everything went off peacefully.
Lord Krishna's blessings, mother.
I've to go back,
host the Kauravas,
And marry Lakshmana Kumara.
-You?
-Yes mother, I have to.
Sister-in-law is waking up.
I'll take leave.
Dashed my hopes and spoilt my mind.
I don't want to live.
-Sasi... Sasi...
-Poor girl is still lamenting.
Sasi, look! It's me!
Aunt! How did you come here?
I didn't come.
It's who came to our place.
Me?
Where are we?
Don't get scared, I'll tell you.
Get up dear.
Did you hear me?
Ruin the wedding.
-Chinamaya
-My leader!
Use your magical powers and illusion
And build a guest city
for Kauravas in Dwaraka.
Yes
Spellbound them with your magic.
Hail leader!
-Hey Rambu
-My lord
Use your intelligence and
teach Kauravas a fitting lesson.
-Hosting a wedding is a tough task.
-But ruining it is a piece of cake.
[cheering]
Stop!
Get going!
Where's my brother?
Brother!
Beau got beaten up!
Who is it?
Sasi, how did you come here?
-Stay away.
Calling me now by leaving me in solitude.
-What is this, Sasi?
-Stay away.
Why are you so angry?
Don't you know I didn't take
chances respecting elders' words.
Fair enough! You must get a
good name for respecting elders,
and I must get bad name
for going against elders.
Enough, good bye to you and your love.
Now, it's brotherly love between us.
Sasi! What are you saying?
That's it.
I can't bear your sorrows or
pangs of separation any more.
I promised to marry Lakshmana
Kumara. And I'll stick to my word.
Is it my Sasi who is saying this?
No, I'm a brand new Sasi.
Totally changed.
I'll marry Lakshmana Kumara,
ride on elephant,
-and go to palace in a procession.
-Sasi, what's this nasty?
-Are you possessed by ghost?
-Not ghost but demon.
But now, it's brotherly love between us.
Come brother. Come.
I'm really very lucky, dear.
Krishna, Rukmini,
Balarama, Revathi,
everyone will come to my home for you.
Aunt... where is my brother-in-law?
I'm coming, sister-in-law.
Come, brother.
Did you see, brother?
Leave me to Lakshmana Kumara,
and you take your Sasi.
[chuckles]
Is this Lord Krishna's
instruction too, son?
Yes, mother.
Only God knows how that groom
is going to bear me as a bride.
How about brother-in-law's voice, aunt?
Don't worry about me, sister-in-law,
take good care of him.
Auspicious time is nearing,
I'm leaving now.
Hail mother!
Hail Lord Krishna!
Place it here. Quick.
What's this, master?
This is the plan of the Guest city.
Look...
These are harems.
These are the magical houses.
What are these lines, master?
Build them.
We shall check the errors in
the plan and then execute it.
Alright. Be on it.
But, where is the door to enter inside?
Here, this is the main entrance.
-Main entrance.
-Yes.
It shouldn't be in that
direction. Place it there.
No, that's north. It doesn't come
under the construction standards.
Your construction standards is for
those who can't think on their own.
But not for us.
Anti friends enter from that direction,
so the entrance should be placed there.
Alright. As you say.
Get up.
Close your eyes.
[reciting spell]
[cheering]
Hey Jambu
Astonishing!
Don't praise.
Well master, it's all empty.
Where are the things to
take task our anti friends?
Things? Look yonder!
[reciting spell]
They are serpent jewels.
-These are...
-Am... Aha....
Shh!
[reciting spell]
-These are?
-Dolls.
Shh!
Look at this!
[reciting spell]
-Hail master!
-Shh!
Shh!
[reciting spell]
[music]
[snoring]
Madam Sasirekha!
Madam bride!
It's morning, please wake up.
Madam bride.
[groaning]
Madam... Sasirekha...
why are you staring at me?
I'm your favourite maid.
Yes... you're my favourite maid.
What happened?
Did you have any bad dream?
You gave a loud cry!
Yes, a bad dream,
dreamt of becoming a devil.
It seems my voice too had changed.
-Have I got back my original voice?
-Yes, madam.
Please be gentle, other maids are scared.
Oh maids!
Why are you afraid of me?
Oh!
What's this?
Who put a broken pedestal here?
Poor girls! Don't shout at them.
I could've been little
subtle. Maids, come.
Madam, you appear very strange today.
Do you think I'm still that old Sasirekha?
No. I'm the fiance of Lakshmana Kumara.
It means my husband is the
future king and I'm the future queen.
Shh! You shouldn't say like that madam.
Look, your mother Revathi is coming.
Mother? Oh God! Mother!
Hail mother, I bow to you.
Is this true?
Did you see her Rukmini?
Mother Rukmini! I bow to you.
-Hail Krishna!
-Bless you!
Have we become strangers already, Sasi?
You're showing so much respect.
I'm just following your advice.
Let it be anyone's advice dear,
you've become obedient.
That's enough for me.
Krishna, I'm really very happy.
If you conduct this
marriage with a great fanfare...
As you say sister-in-law.
You will see it.
Bless you!
[trumpets]
[music]
"Welcome... There's no one to
match your greatness"
"There's no one to match your greatness"
"You're the most
righteous and blessed guests"
"Accept our hospitality
befitting your status and honour"
"Only you can match yourselves"
"All this grand welcome is for you"
"Welcome"
[music]
"Welcome bridegroom"
"We are very fortunate to find you"
"You're the best son-in-law
amongst those in all the realms"
"Get down from the palanquin"
"All this grand reception is for you"
"Welcome"
Crowns...
Diamond studded crowns.
Tough crowns.
"Wear this crown and look innovative"
"Look innovative"
"These are the crown which
protects your head and hair"
"Come forward and have them, dear guests"
"Ornaments and jewellery"
"New gold medallions"
"Ornaments and jewellery are
the relations of beauty"
"Strange sarees and veils"
"...are relations of good lives"
"Come forward and have them, dear guests"
"Footwear is good for dancing"
"Dancing wherever you wear"
"Dancing wherever you step"
"-Dancing wherever you wear"
"-Dancing wherever you step"
"They won't let you
stand but dance always"
"Footwear is good for dancing"
Did you see the lavishness
of the Yadavas, uncle?
This fortune, these riches,
this exhibition,
I think they did this to upstage us.
Any doubt in it, Duryodhana?
When Krishna promised
to conduct the marriage,
I expected this grand affair.
Whatever they may do,
it's nothing compared to your riches.
Well said, uncle.
We are blessed along with you, Lords.
We're received the same grand
reception and hospitality as that of you!
"Who can match this grandeur?"
"Greater than every king of this world!"
"People not seeing this
grandeur have wasted their lives."
"This is what you call prosperity."
"Your kinsman's riches,
run out of words to praise it!"
Shh!
What's this nuisance, uncle?
You both are scholars but
have no common sense.
-As you say.
How dare you praise
others before your lord?
Our mistake.
Please forgive us, lord.
We got emotional and blurted out truth...
Though it's true, never praise others.
We are grooms' side.
Behave highhandedly!
Finding faults in everything,
irritate them.
-Got you lord.
-What did you get?
Watch out now!
We'll torture your kinsmen.
[music]
"Wow! It's my wedding"
"Great! It's my wedding"
"Wow! It's my wedding.
Great! It's my wedding"
"I'll done with you"
"And the world would be in chaos"
"Wow! It's my wedding"
"Great! It's my wedding"
"Wow! It's my wedding.
Great! It's my wedding"
"I'll done with you"
"And the world would be in chaos"
"They say they are the greatest
warriors and the wealthiest of all"
"Our marriage party has
come sobbing aloud"
"They say they are the greatest
warriors and the wealthiest of all"
"Our marriage party has
come sobbing aloud"
"Whoa! Ha ha ha"
"Wow! It's my wedding"
"Great! It's my wedding"
"Wow! It's my wedding.
Great! It's my wedding"
"I'll done with you"
"And the world would be in chaos"
"They say I'm very delicate maiden"
"And the groom will get
enchanted upon seeing me"
"Oh no! Ha ha ha"
"Wow! It's my wedding"
"Great! It's my wedding"
"Wow! It's my wedding.
Great! It's my wedding"
"I'll done with you"
"And the world would be in chaos"
"They say he'll come to tie the knot"
"And I'll feel too shy"
[sings classical]
"They say he'll come to tie the knot"
"tie the knot..."
[clearing throat]
"They say he'll come to tie the knot"
"And I'll feel too shy"
"Play hide and seek game under the veil"
"Ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha..."
-Grandpa!
-What's it son?
-Have we arrived in the guest house?
-Yes. Surely.
You promised to show the
bride to me, where is she?
I'll call her immediately.
I'll send them message that you want
to meet your daughter-in-law.
Revathi will send her daughter happily.
Okay, even I'm eager to meet her.
What if she feels shy to meet him?
She can't be a brave
wife if she feels shy,
I'll not only see her,
I want to talk to her.
-My word is
-irrevocable.
-I know it. I'll send a message.
-As you wish.
[chewing sounds]
Shh!
We are the wedding hosts.
-We shouldn't mess with people of kinsmen.
-Okay.
What kind of wedding hosts are you?
You look like barls.
-Aargh!
-Shh!
What shortcoming did you find
in our reception, guests?
Shortcoming at peaks!
Come with us, we'll show you.
Such a cheap blankets for us?
-What?
When we gave this to maid servants
of our village, they've discarded them.
Respected guests,
we're aren't aware of your status.
Just order us what you
want, we'll arrange it.
-I want silk blanket.
-Okay.
-I want silk carpet.
-Oh! Okay.
Just don't say okay.
-Silk carpet... got it?
-Okay.
Hello wedding hosts,
what are you doing here?
We want fans there and
young maidens to blow it.
-What a wish!
-What a nasty wish!
-What nonsense?
-Get out!
-Do you know who I am?
-Do you know who we are?
Shh!
You're getting angry unable
to understand the language.
What he said means great!
You're scholars,
don't you know it?
We were just getting it,
you said it.
I'll tell the meaning of other word.
The other word means respect.
Am I right?
Yes...
[chuckles]
Is it that?
-Yes, it is that.
Then come here.
Such a cheap cot for a
respected man like me?
Foam bed.. Foam bed.
-I want foam bed.
-Foam bed? We'll get it.
What are you waiting for? Go get it.
As you wish.
-How is it?
-Great! Promised to get it.
They're going to get a foam bed.
Your ancestors must come down.
Well played with them.
-Mother-in-law! I bow to you.
-Get up dear.
I'm happy that you're going
to be my daughter-in-law.
Yes, you're Dhritharastra's
daughter-in-law and I'm yours.
I'm very happy.
Oh, it's hexed Grandpa!
I bow to you Shakuni grandpa.
-Bless you.
-Thank you.
Oh! Why have you displayed the
things that are eye-catching?
-They're for you, take a look.
-Really?
Oh my goodness!
They are more delicate than me.
A touch broke the jewel,
I've lots of much stronger jewels.
Yes, dear.
You're jovial without being ashamed.
I'm happy.
Your groom wants to meet you.
Let's meet him, come.
Then I too have a condition.
If you want me to meet groom,
you must show your skill.
Good granddaughter,
but I've many skills.
-Which one shall I show you?
-Why anything else?
I want to see you play dice.
Play, else I'll not meet the groom.
Grand daughters are like this,
playing fun with grandpas.
Okay, I'll play only once.
Tell me your number.
Two!
If I lose I'll not meet the groom.
-You've started again, then I'll not...
-No... no... play it. Two!
One!
What?
Ah! Two!
Two... Yes, it's two.
If one becomes two,
then six will become three.
We both have won.
Grandpa, you play dice very well.
Isn't that groom near the lake?
I'll meet him. Come Myna.
Why is she behaving like this?
Is Sasirekha an illusionist or
was it a flash that blinded my eye?
Looking at her behaviour and
attitude, my son may...
No need to fear.
Our Lakshmana is her perfect match.
[birds chirping]
[sniffing]
[clears throat]
Awe!
[chuckles]
"O beauty, you're one of a kind"
"You're one of a kind"
"Your beauty and charm is all mine now"
"O beauty... O beauty"
"O beauty, you're one of a kind"
"Distance"
"Why stay away from me, my dear?"
"I'm the Aryan who has
come to marry you"
"Why stay away from me, my dear?"
"I'm the Aryan who has
come to marry you"
-"We are getting married grandly tomorrow"
-Oho!
"O beauty... O beauty"
"O beauty, you're one of a kind"
"We are getting married grandly tomorrow"
"O beauty... O beauty"
"You've to wait till tomorrow"
"Why are you stopping me
and shrouding yourself?'
"Your beauty has taken over me"
"Why are you stopping me
and shrouding yourself?'
"Your beauty has taken over me"
"Your reluctance is increasing
my romantic pain"
"O beauty... O beauty"
"O beauty, you're one of a kind"
"Your reluctance is increasing
my romantic pain"
"O beauty... O beauty"
What to do if it increases?
Elders are here.
"Why are you holding back
citing elders, O maiden..."
"I'm your husband, ain't I?"
"Why are you holding back
citing elders, O maiden..."
"I'm your husband, ain't I?"
"Your kisses and sweet talk are all mine"
[chuckles]
"O beauty, you're one of a kind"
"Your kisses and sweet talk are all mine"
"O beauty... O beauty"
"O beauty... O beauty!"
-Welcome sirs!
-Please taste it.
Welcome
Not there sir, look here.
Vada, stuffed balls,
pheni, sweet chapattis,
stuffed cookies, laddus and jilebis.
They are just plain sweets.
Tamarind rice, various flavoured rice.
They are just rice related bard items.
Almond pudding, cashew pudding,
and various other puddings.
Many varieties of juices and shakes.
They are just drinks.
Brinjals, lady's finger,
ridged gourd and pumpkin.
Enough! They're just vegetables.
Where's the actual delicacy?
That one! We'll get it.
Wait! What is it?
What are you bringing?
Human flesh!
Shh!
Oh God!
Did you think us as demons?
If you're humans, tell us what you want?
What should we say?
You seem like barlish wedding hosts.
The most important dish in
any civilised feast is missing.
Don't torture us, tell what it is?
Want to know?
Tangy tasting leaves, 'Gongura'.
Offering of Goddess Shakambari Devi.
It is the delicacy of Andhra. The king
will not eat lunch without it. Got it?
Do you know what is 'Gongura'?
We know sir. We'll get it heaps.
Please come sir.
[sniffs]
"Ha ha ha. A wedding feast!"
"A wedding feast with
exquisite delicacies"
"It's the Kinsman's feast!
I'm the first honoured guest"
"A wedding feast with
exquisite delicacies"
"It's the Kinsman's feast!
I'm the first honoured guest"
"Ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha"
"Wow! Mouth watering soft vadas
and tasty stuffed balls"
"Here's pleasing hard vadas...
Ha ha ha"
"Everything here is enough for me"
"A wedding feast with
exquisite delicacies"
"It's the Kinsman's feast!
I'm the first honoured guest"
"Ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha"
"Enticing laddus, dainty pheni
and stuffed sweet chapattis"
"I'll tempting jilebis first!
Ha ha ha"
"This feast is only for me"
"A wedding feast with
exquisite delicacies"
"It's the Kinsman's feast!
I'm the first honoured guest"
"Ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha"
"Great papads,
alluring tamarind rice and mashed gram"
"Puddings are real treat!
Ha ha ha"
"Everything is enough for me"
"A wedding feast with
exquisite delicacies"
"It's the Kinsman's feast!
I'm the first honoured guest"
"Ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha"
[guzzling]
Shh!
[casting spell]
Who the hell are these wedding hosts?
Why are you taking so much
time to get 'Gongura'?
What's this Sharma?
All the vessels are empty.
-Where's the tamarind rice?
-Empty.
-Curd rice?
-Sweet pudding?
-Empty.
-Laddus?
-Jilebis?
-Empty.
-Vadas?
-Hard vadas?
-Empty.
Oh, Sharma! They have insulted us.
Let's complain with
Shakuni and take them to task.
Let's teach them a lesson.
What are you looking for?
Empty vessels only. Come, Sharma...
[casting a spell]
By the way, you liked the bride, lord?
Not just like,
I got bewitched by her beauty.
I fell in love with her, desired her,
and sang a song too.
-What about the bride?
-Bride? Silly bride!
She asked me stay away
saying elders are there.
Told me to wait till tomorrow.
How can I wait till tomorrow, Sarathy?
You're strong and great,
Abhimanyu would be dead by now.
-Well said, Sarathy!
-Why Lord?
Nothing.
They get stuck on joining.
They ate the feast themselves
and kept empty vessels for us.
Did you see?
-Sharma
-Shastri
-Oh! Hard vadas!
-Hard vadas!
-Stuffed sweets.
Come here.
I told you to play with kinsmen,
are you playing with me?
-Are you possessed by ghost?
-No...
What's that? I've been watching
you since coming here,
you seem to losing your senses,
if you don't start behaving sensibly,
I'll get you a good head massage.
Be careful!
Okay okay!
-Sarma.
-Yeah
-What is this?
-Hand.
-How many are these?
-Three!
Pinch me.
Then...
-Want carpet.
-Shh!
Abracadabra!
[laughing]
-Shh!
Abracadabra!
[laughing]
-Shh!
Foam bed!
We want foam bed.
Shh!
Abracadabra!
[laughing]
Shh!
[door opened]
Enemies are coming.
-Oh god!
-Aah!
Was the feast thing a magic
or an illusion or a spell?
-What do you say?
-Nothing, pure hallucination.
-You think like that?
-Yes.
Is it carpet?
They removed smaller one
and laid a bigger one.
They thought it's a bigger carpet.
Their ancestors must come down for it.
[laughing]
-Betel leaves!
-Let's have them!
[chuckles]
[chuckling]
Sarma...
What we saw, vanished away.
What vanished, appeared again.
-Do you think this is also hallucination?
-Yes, hallucination only.
-Whoa?
-Oh!
-Yeah [chuckles]
-Eh?
Nah!
-Reason for this hallucinations?
-Nothing much, a form of madness.
What's this?
-Carpet is new one.
-Yes yes!
-So it's rollong up.
-Yeah.
-Let's spread it.
[groans]
Stay!
-Oh god!
-No!
-Oh no!
-Sarma!
[groans]
Is this hallucination too?
This is delusion.
-Oh god! We are dead Sarma!
-Oh my god!
-Sarma! What's this now?
-This is death illusion.
Sarma! We don't need any
illusion or carpets, let's go.
[groans]
Sarma!
-Oh!
-Ah!
[howling]
-Sarma!
-Oh god!
Foam bed!
- Foam bed!
Carpet trouble is over
but foam bed is great.
It's awesome!
-Oh man!
-Aah!
-Ouch!
[groans]
Oh no!
-Oh god!
-Aah!
[groans continue]
[music]
-Oh!
-Whoa!
[knocks]
Sarma! Sastry! The door.
Hey guys! Open the door.
[knocks]
Oh!
Open the door!
Open it... open it.
I know how to... wait!
-Oh Shiva!
Sarathy? Is it you who fell?
Fell? I was doing somersaults.
- Is it? Get up.
Why are you sitting in a corner
leaving the carpet and foam bed?
-Oh! That's for men like you.
-Please, go ahead.
Okay.
-Oh Shiva!
What's this?
Is it a place to keep your slippers?
-Do you've any sense?
-No, we didn't keep it there.
If not, did they come here on their own?
Maybe, we didn't see.
Wow! Foam bed!
What a luxury!
Amazing! Heavenly!
What a great comfort!
Did you see the foam bed?
Heaven... it's heaven.
Oh God!
Just a while ago,
you laughed loud at me.
Now, it's nothing. Very good.
Oh no! Ouch! Oh God!
Oh God!
-May you be blessed with peace!
What brings you at this hour?
After meeting the bride, I'm confused.
I feel like cancelling this marriage.
Did you see? That's Krishna's magic.
He made Sasi to act like this
so that we'll cancel
this wedding ourselves.
Can we fall into his trap?
Let the marriage be over,
everything would come in line.
Understood, mother?
At the same time when I
tie the knot over there,
Abhimanyu should do the same
here and it is Lord Krishna's order.
In my brother's absence?
No need to doubt it,
he'll be here as well as there.
Omnipresent.
I'll go now and ruin that wedding,
I'll be here with Balarama and others
in time to bless the new couple.
I'll purify our ashram, mother.
Do it son, I'll appreciate you.
Hail Lord Krishna!
[trumpets]
[wedding percussions]
"We are happy that"
"Sasirekha is the bride"
"We all are happy that"
"Lakshmana is the bridegroom"
"As Kauravas and Yadavas become kinsmen"
"Marriage festivities are
going on with great fanfare"
"We all are happy that"
"Sasirekha is the bride"
"Abhimanyu is the bridegroom"
[chanting]
For me...
-Who are they?
-Our brothers!
For me...
What's your objection?
Remove the screen.
You mustn't say like
that, they may feel bad.
I don't care, I'm the groom.
I've every right to see the bride.
Grandpa, father-in-law,
get the screen removed.
What's your problem, son?
Why a screen hurdle between
me and the bride?
Get it removed.
What is he saying?
Nothing, it's not our tradition
to hold the screen for so long.
That's it.
But I think following our
traditions in our place is justified.
Which ever place it may be,
let it be done as they wish.
That's what I'm saying. Remove the screen.
Wonderful, Karna!
Our boy has established our supremacy.
I've told you long ago that
Lakshmana has more pride than father.
Karna, I feel pity on
seeing Krishna's predicament.
It's not yet over, the worse has to come.
Carry on the function
according to our traditions.
As you say, okay.
First the bride and groom
must stamp each other's feet,
after that pressing hand.
Shastri, what's that nonsense?
My lord, you must stamp on the toe of
the bride's left leg with your right leg.
Well, I'm ready for it.
You mustn't feel so shy.
You must also do it to him.
What if he gets angry?
Why would I get angry? I'm ready for it.
[chanting]
-Now, the bride must press your toe.
-No objection.
Ouch! Oh my God!
You killed me... killed me...
What about you when you stamped my toe?
Shastri and Sharma, I have to press
the hand, right? Tell her to do it.
-You know to vedic science too, right?
-Yes, I do.
-Now, bride must press your hand.
-No need.
No, you mustn't say no.
Give your hand to her.
[bones cracking]
Ouch! Oh no!
-My hand!
-What do you want?
-I want turmeric-rice to bless.
-Turmeric rice to bless?
It's last in the program.
What's all this, Krishna?
Modern time youth are like that, brother.
Son-in-law, my daughter is little scared,
do it little slowly.
If scared, she can't be a brave wife.
Shastri and Sharma, continue.
Wow uncle! He gave a
good repartee to Krishna.
Keep this jaggery and cumin
seeds on the bride's head. [chanting]
I know.
[gibbers]
Monkey... Monkey
Father, monkey...
-What's this, Lakshmana?
-Monkey!
-What is it?
-Monkey, grandpa.
Come with me.
Why are you calling
a beautiful girl as monkey?
Is it time to romance?
Go ahead.
Keep it on her head.
[chanting]
[sneezes]
Can't you hold it back?
Go ahead, finish it.
[sneezes]
I think it is due to change of water.
These sneezes doesn't mean anything.
Carry on.
-Pity! Change of water.
-Pity!
[wedding percussions]
[roars]
Oh my God! Tiger! Tiger!
Father, tiger...
-What's this Lakshmana?
-Tiger...
-It's not tiger, he's Krishna.
-Yes, son-in-law.
Mother! What's this humiliation?
I don't know, dear.
I don't know what sin I've committed?
Didn't you see the groom earlier, dear?
Why didn't you tell me, Duryodhana?
Is your son having any mental issues?
Forgive me, our prince is a brave warrior.
I'm surprised to see him so scared.
I think it is the work of
black magic of our enemies.
You know its solution, right?
Smear sacred ash and tie an amulet.
Come here.
-This is holy armour!
-This will protect you.
No matter what, I don't want to marry her.
Tiger... Tiger...
If you refuse,
I'll get her married to Abhimanyu.
-No away, I want her.
-Then, come.
[chanting]
Awe!
De... Devil!
Lakshmana...
Uncle!
Son...
Oh! Prince has fainted.
[screams]
Laksmana...
Oh! Our prince has fainted.
-Immediate duty?
-Get him out of it.
No use.
He'll not wake up till this
magical illusion is broken.
What's all this, uncle?
I suspected foul play when
Krishna supported this marriage.
Uncle... uncle...
Don't disturb him.
I must know the truth.
Sathyaki, get me the plough.
Calm down Balarama.
l swear on my dice and tell you the truth.
Listen.
We usurped kingdom of Pandavas by
cheating them in the game of dice.
They kept their promise
and went into exile.
You came rushing to punish us
on hearing this.
But you're a barlish innocent Yadava.
I know you'll easily fall for
praise and felicitation.
You did fall for it.
Though you're not equal to us,
do you know why we insisted on
accepting your daughter in marriage?
lf Pandavas attack us
after the exile period,
to keep you and your brother
away from joining their ranks.
Like as you sow so you reap,
we did got a good stick for it.
Krishna, these cheats shouldn't
be left with this punishment,
-Where's my plough?
- Brother!
Elder uncle, I bow to you.
You needn't have to strain yourself,
I'm here to finish them.
-Who are you?
- Me? Who am I?
When you were arrested by Angels,
Arjuna who came to release you free,
I'm his elder brother Bhima's son.
ls it you Ghatotkacha?
Karna... Dushyasana... hold him.
[chortles]
Hey you Duryodhana, Dushyasana, Karna!
You evil minded people!
Weapons are protecting their
honour by not coming out.
[chortles]
I'll teach you a lesson.
Lambu and Jambu show
them your powers.
[people shrieking]
Duryodhana, you were arrogant
about your wealth.
Watch out, what happens
to your wealth.
Chinnamaya!
[reciting spell]
[people shrieking]
[people shrieking] Fire...
Save us... save us...
Their cries are music to my ears.
Cowards! I'll not kill refugees.
Lambu and Jambu, tie the Kauravas
and dump them in Hastinapuram.
[reciting spell]
[people shrieking]
This is my last warning
to your evil quartet.
"You who have the haughtiness
because of wealth"
"The time is approaching where
your pride brings destruction."
"Go and live a life with senses."
"One more advise."
"Not only the Pandavas,"
"but also their crores of relatives,"
"and their relatives of relatives,"
"this is the punishment if you
go against any of them."
"Remember these words of Ghatotkacha."
[chortles]
l bow to you,
please forgive me uncle.
Bless you.
Krishna, I never expected
Bhima's son will be so clever.
By the way, where's our daughter?
Krishna! Where is Sasi?
Son-in-law!
l bow to you.
A request to elder aunt.
Sasi and Abhimanyu got married
in the same fixed time in my home,
you must come, bless them
and be my guests.
Why are you still here? Let's go.
Come brother.
Sister-in-law Hidamba!
My daughter got married in your home.
Wherever the marriage may take
place, I don't have any objections.
Repeating my words to me.
Come dear.
Subadhra,
I'm handing my daughter happily to you.
Whatever it is, my son is
responsible for this to happen.
That gives me immense happiness.
No mother... no.
This was Lord Krishna's blessing.
Hail Lord Krishna!
"Hail absolute truth...
Hail lord reclining on serpent..."
"Hail destroyer of evil...
hail the saviour of poor..."
"Hail protector of devotees...
Hail lord of illusion..."
"The divine ploys you play"
"Whoever writes or sees them"
"be blessed with prosperity..."
"...and will stay blessed
and happy forever"