(English Subtitles)
A Northern legend of bravery
After fathers death this
cellar was never opened
Yes, Mother told me that too
Uncle's battle dagger
Bamboo nail instead
of iron nail
The treachery is hidden
by gold coating
This is where the
lamp rod was kept. See !
Mom told me uncle recorded
it all on palm leaves, Aunt ?
"What can I say, Father"
"Of the Aringodan's play"
"He injured me no more
than a seed could"
"But cousin Chandu,
he did betray"
"Exhausted from the
weariness of battle"
"On Chandu's lap, I lay "
"Lazily I closed my eyes"
"That moment, Chandu transformed"
"He took the lamp rod"
"and pointed it at me"
"When I snapped to my senses"
"Chandu had taken
Aringodan's side"
"Oh Father, it was Chandu's treachery !"
"Oh Archa, it was Chandu's treachery!"
"Father, it was Chandu's treachery.
Archa, it was Chandu's treachery"
Who's that?
Kunjunuli
Has Mattan come to
test me in my old age?
Aromini arrived from Atumanmel.
Your grandson and Kannapunni are sparring.
Yes, let them play
After my son Aromal died, I havent
heard the clang of a shortsword
Granddad, its me,
Aromal Unni.
Where's Archa
Mom's lighting the lamp
in outer compound
What's the meaning of these
red marks and battle outfits?
Puturan and Atumanmel houses
have no shortage of wealth, but we lack in men.
You kids neednt win us fame/wealth
through battle. Ok?
But a debt remains
unpaid, Dad.
Your mom would say:Men of Puturan are
shortlived as sacrifical goats. How true.
Who are you in search of ?
One who murdered his brother.
He still lives on in Kolathiri.
I'm disgusted to
speak his name.
At Karaparambu, Nambiars insulted
my son in front of hundreds
"Avenge Your uncle first. Then
speak of bravery" they said
He asked me about it,
so I told him the stories.
Why did no one tell me of this treason?
Is it true you insisted Dad beg his cousin
for help even when he mistrusted him?
Yes. Not just me.
Everyone insisted.
I never thought he'd betray me.
Me, who fed him from childhood.
Hope you haven't
forgotten my oath
Sis-in-law, let Kanapan assist Aromal Unni.
Bless their quest, Father.
You want the Chekavars to be
wiped out through revenge ?
Aromal Unni's spirit
is unavenged, Dad.
The shortsword still trembles
in the cellar, Dad.
I know how Kannapunni fights.
And u?
Have you learnt the moves ?
I think so. He mastered advanced moves
from a Tulunad school.
That's not enough
to win battle, kids.
Archa. They cannot beat Chandu.
He must acknowledge
Puturan house is still alive.
Is there a move u
havent taught anyone, Dad?
This move depends on
the enemy's anticipation.
When you begin the stance,
he must assume he is safe.
That's the only way to win.
When his head falls, tell him
I granted you this move.
He never expects
someone to avenge Puturan house
Traitor Chandu
(Prays)
Respects to my Guru.
2 boys, waiting
at the gate.
They insisted on
'personally meeting chekava warrior'
Didnt you tell them
I stopped teaching long ago.
Have they come to learn, or teach me?
Dont know. They didnt tell
their names or intentions.
Young men now try to earn fame by
trying to beat Warrior Chandu.
I wont meet anyone.
Close the gate.
It's not right for Chekava warriors
to close doors on visitors.
We came to
become Your disciples
We dont teach here.
We teach at 17 other schools.
Where're you from?
-Karuthenar
Oh, I know the place. Which house ?
-Puturan house
Puturan. you are..?
Kanapunni, son of Aromal Chekavar
Would be easier if
u told Your mother's name.
Aromal often 'granted' sons to 'lucky women'
when he saw his chance.
My Dad has a single lawful wife:
my mother, Kunjunuli
Oh, Kunjunuli's son. So the son
from Mikavil would be Your senior.
His name?
-Unni kannan
And you ?
His nephew.
Atumanmel Kunjiramans son.
Son of Unni Archa eh.
Kids, you may return. I cant teach you more
than what Elder Kanapan has.
How is he now ?
We didnt come to catch up.
-Then?
To avenge Your murder
of my uncle.
Brace urself, chekava !
Oh. Did Your Mom give you last advice?
No tips on how to
face the murderous warrior ?
I recall she advised me
when I assisted Aromal once.
She told me it is
glory to die in battle.
Only UnniArcha can say that.
Her tongue is anyday sharper than a sword.
Did she promise
a glorious funeral clothed in silk?
Dramatic inspirational
words are her forte.
Your Dad can show-off his
wife with the famous song:
"I'm a woman, but I tremble not.
Why do you men cower?"
I pity Your dad Kunjiraman.
Keep insults for after
the battle, Chandu uncle.
'Chandu uncle'
What do you know of the betrayals of 'traitor Chandu'
- Plenty
"Chandu, who replaced the iron nail with bamboo. Bribed the blacksmith to hide it in gold"
"Chandu, who lied that he forgot the replacement sword"
"Chandu, who stabbed the tired warrior with a lamp body, and then jumped to his escape."
What other betrayals do the bards sing of in Your land?
All you heard is true. And false.
Give them tender coconut and jaggery. Let the kids rest. And then leave.
I shall not fight.
'He who mastered all moves' is afraid ?
Our weapon is not a lamp. We wield a warriors weapon. Sword. And grand-dad's moves.
Does Chandu the warrior kill only sleeping warriors through cheating ?
He wont fight. Will you eat something?
-Stop distracting us.
Are you still testing me, family deity ?
They said they dont want food, that's not what they came for.
Yes. They will not return without settling it. It's in their blood. They only recall how Aromal was beheaded by the unbeatable Aringodan.
You despise me too, isnt it, Kuttimani ?
No need. you always despise or fear me.
No, you've always been kind.
Kind? I'm sorry I replaced love with kindness for the last 18 years.You dont understand me either. No one does.
Not Your fault. Because I never gave you a chance. But I wish someone would understand me well now.
I was an orphan. At 5, my uncle adopted me. Now he too wants me beheaded.
I'd hoped all was forgotten. Now they come and put salt on the wound. The young generation now. Why ?
And they're blessed by my guru. My foster father. My..
Good of you to come help with the funeral, chekava
There's no one else to help, right.? I will take him.
Chekava offered to foster him when sis died., but he didnt agree.
He was stubborn. I know he was poor, but why should he fight the Malayan for 32 gold ?
The dead should not be accused, but..
Marrying Vamakshi to Elamthalam itself was a mistake. Lets not speak anymore.We will leave.
Lets go. He's tired,carry him, Kunjammar.
The famed Puturan house. They loaned even to the Menons and goldmerchant Chettiyars. Mom tearfully recalled her childhood there.
And she'd curse the Gods for her marriage to poverty of Elamthalam.
Their 16 schools were given 2001 gold annually by the ruler. Rulers recruited their soldiers from Puturan first.
Come, son.
This is also Your house. Here's Your aunt.
Unni, here's someone to play with.
Give it to me, it's mine.
-No I wont
Aromal, give it to Archa.
-Dad, this was a Vishu gift to me.
Ok, I'll give you another. Let her have it.
Aromal, this is Your cousin, Chandu.
Go play with the kids. This is home.
You have another playmate inside. Atumanmel Kunjiraman.
Yes. The kids are ready to begin their education on Vijayadashami. you must also learn to write and fight well, eh ?
Here, kids played boardgames with real gold? For a poverty striken me, this dint feel like home,even if uncle tried.
(Prompting) Ahead.. Swing out.. Legs forward.. Kick with the right..
Move, Kunjiraman. Now I will spar with cousin.
(Prompting) Lift right knee.. Swing hip.. Ahead.. Change foot..
Enough.
You got stubborn, and lost it.
You learned up 9 basics in a month. Smart boy.
He thinks he is great.
- Why is Chandu still here?
Dad brought him because he has no food. Many people mooch off us anyway. Let him also stay.
I prayed everyday. "Oh Goddess and war gods. Let the day come when they sing my praises as a warrior."
"Give me strength in my arms. In my weapons."
Mom, who is that child?
Thumbolarcha, from Mikavil Mikacheri.
You Ambady people are here too. Why did you not get Kunjunni engaged ?
The ones in a hurry can go ahead.
Where is Chandu ?
Change Your clothes. Kunjamar ?
Oh Child Lord Ganapathy, oh black Snake wargods !
Give them a happy marriage. Give them victory wherever they go.
Ear pierced at 5 years age. Learnt Your alphabet at 7.
You shall learn Your skills well. Tie the knot at 10.
They're our future. They will be warriors.
Guard the land. Win the battles.
Ear pierced at 5 years age. Learnt Your alphabet at 7.
You shall learn Your skills well. Tie the knot at 10.
Bring the flowers, bring the instruments.
Bring along a thousand people to celebrate.
(Prompting)
You promised to return by year-mid. Where were you ?
I was given a good piece of land, where I built a school. 57 feet. A little bigger than this place.
For good teachers, 50 feet will do. Your body becomes Your eyes, Your weapons become Your mind.
You threw out Your basics in Your hurry to build a school, didnt you Kunjirama ?
Watch him.
So, what's special about him?
To you, a weapon is something you hold. To him, a weapon is part of his mind. That's all.
Aromal, I own 6 schools. After you master footing, I'll appoint you as guru in 3 of them.Students from afar will come on hearing Your name.
We'll take only registration fees.You can claim the tuition fees for urself.
Chandu's the one who assists elder in his fights, isnt it?
-Sometimes.
So the nephew is teachers pet ?
-Says who ?
The tons of praises pouring out from Your father the critic.
-Let spectators decide who's better, at the public show.
Lets keep a wager during the public show. you versus Chandu.
Winner gets a golden snake-necklace from me. The guru neednt know of this.
I know you practise alone these days.
Your dear bro is always a step ahead. I must catch up, if not beat him.
You're already ahead. We both know that.
Hold on.
Checking if this is still here.
Let our 'footing' exam be done. We will work on improving Your strength.
Someone has asked Your brother to turn the public practise into a competition.
Who?
Whoever it is, I wont compete. Not because I'm a coward, but because this is a wrong time and place. So not now.
Aromal !
Competent, arent they?
The nephew is stronger.
Thats enough. Its not battle, its a show. Which of you forgot it first ?
Now Puturan house boasts 3 Chekava warriors.
You must improve Your footing. you still have time to learn.
You must become better than Your dad. I was observing Your handsomeness, I didnt observe Your moves.
That is Puturan house. Male or female,beauty is in their blood.
Footing is the most important thing. I think the son beats the nephew in that.
Wait.Extend Your hand.
Did it hurt?
- Yes. But its fine. When you deviate from the planned routine show, you must declare it. Thats the rule.
Well, you must know how to defend those.
-You're Elder's son, so no one blames you. Atleast uncle knows.
Even if I declare my moves, you cannot defend them, cousin.
-Want to try now ?
Now there's no one to appreciate Your beauty. Come.
Chandu. Dont.
Lower Your swords, both of you. Battle is not the way to end it. I will stop this recklessness.
The lords blabber something for the sake of it. Dont bother about it. you did well out there.
You outshined Aromal.
I am satisfied.
That's all I ever need to hear.
My foster-dad, guru and god. Uncle was all that.
The ones who want to behead me, come with His blessings.
Once, they all went to the Karivel festival. I was alone.
The beats of Uncle's praises rang in my head. My mind was satisfied, and celebrating its own festival.
Please serve dinner for me. I shall sleep early.
Shall I heat water for Your bath?
Oh, I thought you were the Mani girl.
Shall I serve u? But can guests serve hosts? Archa might argue against that
I saw Alathoor uncle in the gallery, but couldnt spot you, Kunjunuli
You wouldnt spot me, unless I'm clad in shining swordsteel. Or so I hear from Unni-Archa
I wanted to return. But Dad made me stay.
Good. you Alathoor people rarely visit. Didnt you go to the Karivel fest ?
That's what they invited me for.They need someone to accompany the beauty from Mikavil, dont they. But I refused.
I din't know ThumbolArcha had come either.
Not personally. She sent her servants to announce arrival.
Did it hurt ?
-Its just a cut. Not a problem.
I wanted to give you a gift. Didnt know if it was appropriate custom for a girl to gift at the competition.
So I..
No thanks. I dont like these formalities.
Please leave, Kunjunuli. If Mani sees this..
Or is it UnniArcha you fear?
Yes. I have to live with her someday.
- And you think Archa feels the same way?
"Who wears the scent of sandalwood. Is it the wind, or my lover?"
"Who opens the box of kajal now, is it youth itself, is it a Goddess ?"
"Who does those red lips of yours await today?"
"Your morning prayers are over. Which other God will you worship now?
"Behind your garments, does the pleasure of your bodice awaits my eyes?"
"Who wears the scent of sandalwood. Is it the wind, or my lover?"
"The jewellery you dorn, to me they are arrows from Cupid's quiver."
"The pleats of your garment, why do they playing a game on my eyes ?"
"Her hip-necklace fell away, and the young lass, she stole my heart away".
"Who wears the scent of sandalwood. Is it the wind, or my lover?"
I'm done. You can enter now
Is Dad done with his prayers? I am ready to leave now.
- To go where?
Attumanmel. Arent you coming? They are installing an idol in the school. Aromal will teach there.
I didnt know this. I'm going somewhere too. Elantalam house.
So Attumanamel?
-Not coming. No one invited me.
Does a warrior need an invite to a martial arts school? Is'nt it his right ?
So says logic. I have work at Elanthalam. Kunjammar can manage the rituals at the school here.
What will you do there alone ?
-Well, someday people will be living there, right?
Archa
Archa,your make-up will delay us.
The big puja will be done by the lord of Trichambar.
So you have come.
For a few days. I wanted to clean up the house.
You must start up a school. Else the kids need to cross the river to learn.And that boatman cannot manage.
I will start at an auspicious time. I wanted to ask you, can you lend me 500 gold? Need to buy furniture and vessels.
Wont Puthooran grant you furniture and vessels, when they give their single daughter? Has the date been fixed?
No, uncle has not mentioned to me.
I have seen her once.She is royal and beautiful.The stars shine well upon you.
You may come to Puthanmalika for the money. Let lack of money not delay Your marriage.
Summon the architect.
The Elder asked you to come.
- Why, cant they manage well there?
He didnt mention.
Did Aunty tell u?
-No, I just arrived.
There was work at the school. And I cleaned the house.
Before flagging off Aromal's school, we must get Archa wed.
When they asked her horoscope, Aromal gave it to them.
- To whom?
Aromal did it all. He matched it with Kunjiraman's and fixed a marriage date for them.
Not because they didnt remember about you.
We could rein him when he was a kid. Now we are old.
I had to argue and fight him, asking him to honor his word to his friend. Aunty will tell you.
Son..
-I think I heard enough aunt.
Did she agree as well, UnniKanna? Your sister.
Yes, and no.
No one told me you came. Did Dad tell u?
Aromal fixed everything.
-And you agreed to it and closed the chapter.
I know Elanthalam is not grand enough to fancy a relation with Puthooran. But still my house and school are ready.
I loaned money for it.The architect wouldve prepared the wood by now.
Chandu..
- Di, you are my...
When brother Aromal insists..
- You must obey him.
I have only 1 sister.The bro must plan for her future. 5 farms, 6000 bags of rice, 1 inheritor. Need I ask for more?
Cousin,I was engaged to her in our youth.
-That was just an old-fashioned custom to fool the kids
So anyone may give a word of engagement, then go back on it? Is it Puthooran custom, or one of all warriors ?
Can brother or sister give me an explanation behind this ?
21 gold. Its the only binding term in the contract. That account was to be closed before marriage, and I have done it now.
It is for you to know too.
A Chekava settles accounts with swordsteel, not gold. Come.
Bro, dont.
- Move away !
Aromal, no !
Stop I say.
Just because he said something in anger?
Are you cousins, or monsters?
Both of you, shake your hands and say your apologies.
Are my words falling on deaf ears?
Did my grudge ever die? Frankly, no. She was my love, my thoughts, the hope that ran through my blood since I was 13.
That is what they made me forsake.
Maybe her cousin Chandu didnt deserve her. I wished her to have a good life.
The marriage went well?Dont worry, there r good girls for you out there.
Let us find one.
Chandu insisted I come
Why didnt you turn up for the marriage?
I was at Tulucheri
- Thankfully the marriage plans are moving on.
I have not seen Your daughter, Alathoor.
She's my only daughter.Since Archa is wed,let's not delay this.
That's what I told Chandu too. He has been unlucky so far,like uncle.
Yea. Kannappan told me they'd be here before noon.You people left before them, isnt it ?
They said there'd be 16 people for lunch, so they should turn up soon.
We came for..
-Yes, I know, the cousin came instead of the Father.
Dad, ask them if I should bring coconut water?
-Bring them water to wash themselves.
My daughter is lucky.The Mikavil people tried hard, but ThumbolArcha's horoscope did not match Aromal.
But as fate had it, Kunjunuli's horoscope did match.
Your nephew came early.
- Understandably. By custom, the cousin is the one who is at the forefront of organizing.
The cousin must accompany Aromal throughout the wedding. Thats custom.
Please sit inside.
Enough. I'm convinced. What more can Aringodan's school teach u?
They say a Chekava warrior keeps learning until death.
No one generally likes that last lesson.
I've never seen your famed broadsword styles. And the southern arts.
.. are mere Aringodan tricks. That's what your uncle gossips.
Who's your enemy?You came here despite mastering the Puthooran slashing style, so your enemy is powerful.
I have none, now.
Keep the fees.
Take them.
Thats my daughter, Kunji.
I used to live with my daughter, and now a daughter-in-law joined me. Kuttimani. Chandu, you may live inside the palace.
No need.I can easily reach by early morning.
You may decide as you wish.
So you now see that Aringodans dont do magic tricks?
Your education was incomplete.You chekavas have never faced challenges as big as elephants.
When people ask me if I can tame them,I dont deny either.
"Is it the light of a lamp ? Is it the Labernum flower in bloom"
"Does he come from the sky? Is it the rising sun behind the hills?"
"The beauty of his jet black hair, and the strength of his arms"
"The shapely neck, like a conch. The built body"
"Does he come from the sky? Is it the rising sun behind the hills?"
"The legs with the snake bracelet"
"The warriors beauty on his face"
"Who is the battle hero whose presence fills the arena"
Where to ?
Is UnniArcha at Puthooran or at her husbands house?
- I do not know.
Is Aromal's wedding over?
- Tomorrow.
U've been enquiring on Karuthenar land news.
News from famed lands travels fast to our doorsteps.
Ive been wanting to see Archa ever since I heard of her defeating the men at Nagapuram.
People wonder why she wed that transsexual, Kunjiraman.
Who wonder? The people, or u? Here's the answer.
All girls, including you, you see what no one does. You curse while you flirt. Cry while you laugh. Love while you hate.
If you have any more tactics, please teach me.
And this curiosity to enquire news? That's another tactic. Dont try it against me.
I will return day after tomorrow evening.
I didnt meant to scold you. Sometimes a madness takes me, and I feel like shouting.
Please dont misunderstand. I take my leave.
Chandu, are you still at Elanthalam now?
- Sometimes.
Someone told me the place is closed. I teach at Pudushery school now, you know. The lord insisted.
Pays me 1000 at the beginning, and 1001 at the end.
- Very good for you.
Archa is planning to set up a marriage for you with someone
Aunty, I shall..
- No, dont leave. There's a dinner feast tonight.
Then another feast tomorrow morning. No one's waiting for you back there, so dont run away.
So you escaped to Tulunadu during my marriage. Well timed, how convenient.
How long do you plan to be a loner?
- As long as possible.
Dont you need someone to atleast cook for u?
- I love cooking my own food these days.
Perhaps Your horoscope matches that of ThumbolArcha? Why didnt anyone think of that? Even I hadnt. Shall I enquire?
-No need
Theyre still on good terms with us. The marriage plans were changed because Aromal's horoscope didnt match.
Or is it that the gold in Mikavil is much lower compared to Alathoor uncles ?
Its not for wealth that I... I only did it because Aromal.
-Enough. Its history now. I dont want a narration.
Do you think they showered me in pearls and covered me with gold in that palace?
They consider servants a waste of money,so I do all the work.
Is that all ?
-I have to ask a hundred persmissions to cross the gate.
I must lift every pail of water I bathe with. And when I try to practise my sword slashing, the sound echoes in the house.
Mother advised me not to practise anymore.
Beyond Kumarom river,Elanthalam is close, isnt it?
-Maybe
Why dont you come to me once in a while? In the night at the river, you can hear the sound of passing boats.
Kunjiraman is at Pudusheri 4 days a week.
- I know. He told me his salary too.
Do you hate me so much ? There isn't a single day I didnt think of you. It's all my bad luck.
Do come. I will keep the backdoor open
You are blushing a lot
"The crescent moon has opened her eyes.
Now the day has become complete"
"Gradually, she casts her spell. Gracefully, she enters the lover's chariot"
"Where are the heavenly nymphs? Where are the escorts with golden fans?"
"Like a thousand volcanoes in unision, the song sang..."
"The crescent moon has opened her eyes.
Now the day has become complete"
"Gradually, she casts her spell. Gracefully, she enters the lover's chariot"
"Who's illusion of hope is this?
Who's song of expression is this "
"In a thousand colours, the night dressed herself"
Even yesterday I stayed awake, thinking of you.
Archa..
Get out you indecent fellow. Did you think there were no men in this house ?
Savage !
I opened the backdoor thinking it was you, and he...
That night Chandu earned another title."He who swam a river, rode a horse, to enter a married womans chamber"
"The nymphomaniac, sex-hungry Chandu"
(Chanting)
I am Unichandror, the lord of Kurungattu land in Melur. I have an issue with with my cousin Unikoonar, regarding land.
You may sit and tell me. Start from the beginning.
What is it ?
-Dont worry. They come not to attack, but request.
Chandu, come here.
Do you hear? It started when the ex-ruler of Kurungattu died.He had a son each from 2 wives, but they do not know who is elder.
They gambled gold and silver to settle this, but his cousin won. They had a cock-fight, and he won that too.
- Bad luck..
I know.
- He is a cheat and a liar. He had once agreed in public that I am elder.
In the vendetta that followed, Unichandror lost 4 men.
- And Unikonar lost 8 men.
So they want to settle this by trial by combat. And they want me as their champion
The ruler suggested it was better this way. Trial by combat, rather than all-out vendetta with many innocent casualties.
True. Then there'd be only 1 innocent dead.
- Warrior,thats the way its handled, isnt it?
Yes, thats all a warrior does - kill or die. I am too old for this, better a youngsters. This one's good, he is skilled.
Chandu.
I have not heard of you.
- Nephew of Puthooran, and now my disciple .
Oh, from Elanthalam. Son of the guy who the Malayan killed.
- Yes.
I prefer Aringodan. Then I can rest assured of victory. That's what people tell me.
Did they tell you I try magic tricks on the enemy?
Where is the arena built?
-In Prajapati land, near the city wall.
Who is Unikonar's champion?
-He is searching in other warrior schools.
Bring the battle-gold on Monday. Today is not auspicious. Kelu, tell them the price and formalities. Monday.
May you live long.
Father
- A sword was forged somewhere to behead me.
In battle or not, the sword will find me. So how does it matter ?
Kunji, I have warned you - no flirting or crying in this house. There will be a Ganapathy puja on Monday.
51 lamps in the temple. One for every year that I lived to tell the tale. 51.
And these lords squabble over their banana trees and jackfruits.
Alas, I was born to die, a Chekava warrior.
Dont be scared, you heard what Dad said. I wouldve gone instead of Your Dad.
I didnt mean that.
-1 day I have to.But these people came specifically for Your Dad.
Please go to assist him.
- Let Your Dad decide on that. He has many good disciples.
He doesnt trust their skills much. Maybe thats his nature.
Only one who knows the Aringodan well know him truly. He's used to projecting his harsh image. Too late to change that.
He likes you, Chandu. He considers it lucky you joined him. Right?
Yes, but the real luck is your's.
But the daughter is the really lucky one here.
Will you go assist Dad, as I had asked?
- Let us see when the time comes
May you live long.
- What news, friend
They didnt stop even after I sang praises your praises.
- Who ?
The Elder-younger issue. Unikonar has approached Puthooran house.
This is going to be trouble
Only one child, Aromal, lives here. He isnt fully trained Chekava yet. And I'm not too old, so I shall come.
Those who approach Puthooran never return empty handed.
Well then. If you need someone to face the Aringodan and his magic tricks, search elsewhere.
Please sit, lord. Those who do not stand up to honor my Dad, need not do the same for me.
We..
- Pay the battle fee. I shall come.
Aromal
- They come in search of me. Its not right to say no.
As per custom, here is the gold for the land.
Gold for the house. And your battle gold.
This will scarcely be enough to send letters to my relatives.
Still not enough for a Ganapathy puja.
Now, its barely enough for my battle outfits.
For this much, one of my students will do.
For this,I shall send my cousin Chandu. He is equivalent to me.
You may fix your fee as you wish.
- 100 bags of 1001 gold, if you insist on Aromal coming.
I came to know.
- I want you to assist him. Only then will i feel secure.
In the battle at Alathiyoor, I still remember you spotted and warned me of the enemy's fake footing and diversions.
You were only 17 then. Later...
- Later I joined you for 3 more battles, Uncle.
Aromal doesnt lack in skill. But, that cannot win a battle.
-But, Uncle, I...
Ure the best choice, to spot, parry and shield the enemy moves. I decided on you the moment he took the fee.
What did Aromal say?
- What can he ? I am the one who decides.
He was only unsure whether yoYou're too angry to help him.
He's my nephew, I brought him up. How can he be angry?
Since he took the battle gold, we should not lack in celebrations and customs.
The invitations should go to every land accessible.I will tell the ruler personally.
He is in his school, observing his fast. Go meet him.
While we young men live, it's a shame to send my father into battle. Dont you worry.
This is the fee we took to sell you off, brother. Why give it to me?
If I am destined to die,may it be in battle. Whats wrong.
I bargained gold from the lord, enough for 3 generations of Puthooran. you saw?
May you live long.
May the battle gods bless us.
Uncle insisted I assist you.
- Dad told me. But only fighters who are slow to catch the enemy's moves, need an assistant.
But you will do.
Can I enter?
- Ladies must not enter when the fast is observed.
I saw UnniArcha entered the school.
- I dont know.
If something happens to him..
- Nothing will happen.
If it does,it'll be her loss. I must tell her.
- Who's?
Must I mention? The beauty ThumbolArcha.
- But she is'nt married to Aromal.
Really? So have'nt you heard stories of why Aromal goes there in the nights,on the pretext of gambling?
It seems she has a daughter.
- So this is how honourable those Mikavil folk are.
They began respecting my feelings only recently. But just when I was finding peace, this lord arrives.
Be courageous. Its all fate, Kunjunuli.
Even I wonder about fate. Back then that day, you were a bit late to decide, were'nt you.
Yes. I was late for many things. It's alright now.
Chandu
I am the one always making the mistake.
Stay away.
I know your tricks well.
Now you can start crying. But it wont work.
Whatever you think of me... Dad told me you agreed to assist Aromal. Thank goodness.
I only listened while Uncle asked. I've not decided yet.
- Please do go.When bro enters battle,u must assist.
Its my request, too.
That day,I found no other way to avoid a scandal.
I am still alone.
- I know. When I think of it...
Well, why worry? You once spoke of a good wedding plan for me, didnt u? ThumbolArcha from Mikavil?
Haven't you recommend me to Aunty yet?
- That..
I am okay with it. What say ?
- Brother has started 'visiting' there.
Please go assist brother, make sure he is in no danger. Its my request. I will do anything for that.
Anything?
- Anything.
If you win the battle, I'll be Your girl from that day on. I promise.
Arent you pregnant now?
Thats my fate. Once upon a time, I'd dreamt of bearing your son, secretively.
Why else would I invite you into my bedroom? Even there, my calculations failed.
After the battle, I will tell them this was my promised for the battle. Let Dad and bro undo the marriage.
Some day, UnniArcha's word must be honored.
- Promise?
Promise. On the goddess, on the snake battle-gods, on my Father. I promise.
Archa
Shall I tell Mom and sis-in-law that yoyou've agreed to assist? They can rest peacefully then.
The smith in Kolathiri is skilled.Get him to forge the sword. The fee is 10 gold. Give him 6 more, and a dhoti.
The lord and people will come to send you off for battle. We will join, too. Chandu, you shall wait at Kizhur.
Ok.
- The arena is near the city wall. Inspect it beforehand. I know I need not ask you.
It's a common battle tactic to cheat people by placing broken flooring.
I know. In that battle at Therotta, there was that broken floorplank once.
So you have still not forgotten that battle, eh.
- I've forgotten nothing.
Yes?
- Your opponent is..
I know. But I'd hoped to face Kannappan himself. We must resolve who is greater. Not this time, I guess.
I will be assisting Aromal.
- Treachery. you learnt all of Aringodans moves,and now..
He is his cousin. It's required of him.
I have never feared battle. But this time..
Had you not considered me Your guru as well?
- Yes.
Do you pray for me?
- Yes
Then whose victory do you pray for now?
Because both combatants usually never win.
Need not reply.
If you have time, console my daughters. I'd hoped to get them settled earlier.
Coconut water to drink?
- No. I need to meet the blacksmith. I'd met Your Dad.
Why dont you sit?
- I will be assisting Aromal.
Was'nt it Aromal who spoilt your wedding once?
-Yes, but he is my cousin. Uncle insisted.
Did she insist too? She.
- Archa? Yes.
She still has the brave Chekava at her fingertips.
- Stop, woman. Enough relationship advice.
She knows well that when she whistles to her faithful dog, this brave one will run to her, tail in between legs.
Your Dad is fasting. Pray for him. It will be more useful than Your blabbering.
Please stop. I blabbered as a woman does. My mistake.
- Its ok.
I had hoped you'd assist Dad. But instead, you ended up assisting the opponent, so I lost it.
If something happens to Dad, I will be alone.Dad is waiting for Your approval,do you know?
Approval for what?
- Dad agreed he would conduct the marriage anytime. But he does'nt know how to ask favors.
He guessed correctly what I wished. But some other people realize it only if I shout it out.
I'll always be here to help you 2 and your Dad. After all, he too is my guru.
Will you accept it? For my Dad atleast?
- This is'nt the time to decide, Kunji. I should leave now.
Live long.
I requested the blacksmith to forge it well, using whatever material was required
They a good blade should even cut an elephants tusks.
(Prompting) Defend on backfoot, jump and turn..
Swing backfoot and turn back to face enemy
Swing to the left, then right, jump and slash down
The Aringodan cheated his move, thats why Chandu stopped his stab.
Opponent. I saw that you cheated.
- When you see unexpected moves, dont call it cheating.
How untrained you are.
-Lets see how well I trained.
The first 2 rounds were neck-to-neck. Now this tiebreaker round will decide.
Swing and slash. Swing and sidestep.
Give me the replacement sword, Chandu.
- I need time to get the weapon.
Aringodan, stop. Wait till I get the replacement sword. Its the rule.
Stop, Aringodan. Wait until the replacement arrives.
Unikonar, you may claim your land. Puthooran Aromal has won the battle.
Those who wish to see Aringodan's dead body, come onto the arena.
The cut..
- Is not very deep. It's okay.
The blacksmith cheated us. But the battle gods were on our side. What treachery !
Was it the blacksmith who betrayed, or you, cousin?
Tell the truth.
- Aromal, I wanted you to win this, even more than you did.
I'd always told them you would betray, Chandu.
If they ask me why I killed my assistant, this broken sword will give them an answer.
Stop. If you want to fight me, we shall fix a venue and time, but later.
If I can defeat Aringodan with half a sword, a quartersword will do for you.
Aromal
Lord, Chandu has betrayed me.
Please spare me.
Who bribed you to botch up the sword by replacing the nail. Tell me.
How much did the Aringodan bribe?
Even Aringodan does'nt know of this. We were asked to keep mum about it.
Who asked you to do this?
- The Aringodan's daughter.
When I heard who the opponent was, I hoped the replacement sword would be good enough.
Where is that guy, Chandu?
- He has not come here.
Close the gates.
Move away. Where is she?
- You shall not pass.
Call her out, the traitor who bribed the smith to mess up the sword.
Aromal is the one who cheated. And you stood watching.
How Puthooran it is to throw a halfsword when a battle is paused.
Oh God
Where is she?
- Please dont
Kunji. Open the door.
Archa, what happened is
I can guess what happened, from your face.
Atleast you must know the truth, Archa.
You betrayed my bro, as well as me, who you were engaged to.
If my child is a boy, my brother asked to name it after him. I hope it is a boy.
Archa, listen to me
- No. I dont want to listen or see you anymore
Traitor Chandu. My son will come visit you one day. To avenge his uncle's death.
I promise. On the battle gods, on my dead brother.
Aromal's son and nephew
I am scared.
Kuttimani. Light the lamp in the battle room.
Kuttimani, you may leave
The fight isnt over yet, warrior. Grandfather has taught us more moves.
You call this battle? I humored a game with you immature kids, and you call it battle?
I simply dodged and shielded myself from Your cuts, without a fight.Are you not trained enough to realize, kids?
What other move? The old Puthooran one where you 'fool an enemy into feeling secure, and then trick him'?
Or the new trick from the Kuruppans, where you fling sand into a defending fighter's eyes ?
Take up Your weapon
You cannot defeat Chandu
In life, I've been defeated. Many times. By many people.
My dad first defeated me, when he died at the Malayan's hands.
Then my guru, who feared to show me impartial love.
The girl I loved, as she traded off my love for another's gold. Then finally, my friend, who didnt believe me.
Still Chandu lives on, waiting to be defeated again.
Return
- Aromal's son and nephew didnt come to return defeated
There is no man alive who can beat traitor Chandu. Not by skill, not by strength. No one. You may return.
Kill me if you will. UnniArcha's son has come prepared to die honorably in battle if need be.
Take up your weapon
You must not fail, children. Here ends the story of the traitor Chandu.
Here begins the legend of Aromal Unni who avenged the honor of Puthooran house.
Place my head at your mothers feet, and bow to her. Gather gifts and compliments from the ruler.
Let them cheer Your name out loud. After all, child, you could have been my son. Let them cheer.
Salutations, my guru.